<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>letters on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/tags/letters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in letters on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:16:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/tags/letters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Dog Heads to Chicago</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/brown-dog-heads-to-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:16:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/brown-dog-heads-to-chicago/</guid>
      <description>1416
The following are transcriptions from free legal pads :
 1 day after Bonjo&#39;s Bday CHP chad mic copped a mirage 8 months unregistered never got caught Thank you for letting me freestyle If I freestyle Dub bitch as is motif and hook and all as is hurt dumb bitches hurt dumb bitches I call it as I see it who&#39;e counting anymore 3 months ago I wrote thank God for like why am I even here at this coffeeshop pissed but not before not hurt but hurt but not &#39;way before&#39; written too many times this dude doing database queries smells worse than me I know ause I just smelled myself oh wow the freewrite is over today is recording, last night was recording Andre&#39;s acapella shorts while helen was venmoing ollie 40 bucks for drinks and or food =&amp;gt; her gmail was logged in on my phone &amp;quot;don&#39;t want my name on a basketball&amp;quot; chain and ball 1 lyft 1 uber and I&#39;m douple||triple peed =&amp;gt; patient pissed peeboy who knows why am I sitting here cause seeing her even though I&#39;m triple pee is better than not seeing her =&amp;gt; and today 4 sure is not the day for it But bumping 30 minute freewrite back when I was driving Locatelli&#39;s corolla  Don&#39;t even have to write nor record yet so happy I&#39;m doing both who knew conrete could work so well with lake and looking up at the sky with my finger goggles I though this is way too beautiful for you to not be here Though I&#39;m sure some atrium at Emma&#39;s work would compliment the clouds but here at the lake my ankles spashing carelessly, you can see the currents underwater the deadly rip tows and every good sailor knows looking up at the winds in the clouds is how you can see the currents below I the arrogant swimmer don&#39;t question I suppose up the currents underwater are inline with the wind in the clouds pushing 30 miles an hour thousands of feet above me and the musicians only job is to document capture destroy manipulate over think convolute rule over forget about justify nothing with logic as church no stop - just look up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Rash Wanton</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/terry-rash-wanton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 15:33:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/terry-rash-wanton/</guid>
      <description>do you lose respect for me if I bate right now or gain respect
so I dont bug you
cause its been an hour since we had sex
and I can&amp;rsquo;t hold it
that&amp;rsquo;s why I don&amp;rsquo;t go out by myself
 cause now hours later we&#39;re getting back to our roots just biked to you and we&#39;re starting our night at Volumes Books in Wicker Park I brought us a bottle of Cali Roots and plastic cups we&#39;ll open the bottle with this pen and I&#39;ll get back to writing about my hate of plastic but the plastic in me loves plastic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are a Wonderful Person</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/you-are-a-wonderful-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 16:45:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/you-are-a-wonderful-person/</guid>
      <description>you are a wonderful person too complex a creature to be nailed down on any one person place or thing besides maybe you&#39;ve got the same curse as me patiently waiting for the freedom working towards the freedom of diner hopping going from diner to diner to diner to diner.  Cause when you get to one, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter it it&amp;rsquo;s a desert outside, a busy street, or snowing. Diners stay timeless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Many Pics</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/too-many-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 16:15:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/too-many-pics/</guid>
      <description>the inky only helps my psyche. I&amp;rsquo;m jogging this much I feel. Lovae as capital. Hypothetical house. Pable blue dot fm. Life the musical. Federal beat reserve. What idea is going to get me 3 meals and a cot, a place to record, a beach house for my mom? Everything else will go to pilot&amp;rsquo;s license and the nonprofit turned summer camps music camp orrphange. You know. Brining back the musician in everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>