<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>log on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/tags/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in log on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:26:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/tags/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Banned Words</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</guid>
      <description>..and no bad days == 1750 h got me a beer and we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to freewrite to warm the engines up but I&amp;rsquo;m really just gunning for helping her and then doing god knows what on the website, just the savage new hip hop mantra, results and go go go and things that don&amp;rsquo;t take so long and such == and I got to thinking about this old man here and everyone at the kreautburg we&amp;rsquo;re sitting in and helen&amp;rsquo;s looking at my screen and I&amp;rsquo;m just fucking stoked it&amp;rsquo;s christmas on fucking november sunday 552 pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Mom and Bonnie</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 13:05:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</guid>
      <description>Dear mom and bonnie, I love you, I want to support yo both, but I&#39;m clearly adding stress to both of your lives. I came here to help dad, I was hoping to stay a few weeks, maybe up to xmas to show support and for us to grieve together. It&#39;s too short a time to rent somewhere else in the area, and I need to be in the city to move my career forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up From Strange News From Another Star</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:14:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</guid>
      <description>1015AM
finally a timestamp
\
that was a month where dtme
didnt exits
 death was life and life was death and they were locked together in an eternal mad lmove battle and this was the final word and the meaning of the world and thence came a radiance that could glorify all misery and thence came a shadow that trumpeted all joy and beauty but from out of this darkness joy burned more intimately and more beautifully and love had a deeper glow within this night -from flute dreams by herman hesse (Strange news from a another star)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another One Flies West</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/another-one-flies-west/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/another-one-flies-west/</guid>
      <description>2132 || Been offline never got to get this screen fixed but setup with ted&amp;rsquo;s monitor in the room . been sleeping next to dad since flying back, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s been seven days now. yeah about that really. this is the hardest period of my life. || dads in the hospice bed and I&amp;rsquo;ve been recording every day; people visiting, mom and I taking care of him, music, the nurses, bonnie and her two daughters, phone calls, voicemails, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I in Love or Am I Obsessed</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/am-i-in-love-or-am-i-obsessed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 22:10:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/am-i-in-love-or-am-i-obsessed/</guid>
      <description>am I in love or am I obsessed im all in on her olive shes out two hours Im obsessing my hearts arrest without convitction my hearts arrest accused and not guilty she leave 2 hours its rough and when she finally walks through I&#39;ll hate her and (sub snuff her /sub) that&#39;s that that&#39;s love that&#39;s love and that&#39;s that so am I obsessed or am I in love whats the difference when its reciprocated  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BWall Death of Pauls Hookahs</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/bwall-death-of-pauls-hookahs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/bwall-death-of-pauls-hookahs/</guid>
      <description>painted all day had mugs pizza first time deep dish pep AMAZING
mace practice in the driveway after work and then always sunny, south park, and {{typing put put gold}} :) .
12:13AM
 it&#39;s brick wall bwall hookahs are the shoe brand made for tennis she hated painted all day sacrificed them at a rate constant and look at what you can achieve&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;((archive))&amp;lt;/sub&amp;gt; by not feeding your soul not subscribing to your face mole your face mole that says me what the good word told you and growing grown gone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arp Hats the Machine Makes</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/arp-hats-the-machine-makes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 10:34:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/arp-hats-the-machine-makes/</guid>
      <description>1034AM
just got to nextspace going to work on poliw.at || need a workout there&amp;rsquo;s a gym pass in my bag - studios not free until 2:30 - 3:00
got filmed last night pap andre emma came over and it was a real fun night, did the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Year Old Said GodisFake Then We Ate Two Whole Ducks After Bowling</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/4-year-old-said-godisfake-then-we-ate-two-whole-ducks-after-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 14:28:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/4-year-old-said-godisfake-then-we-ate-two-whole-ducks-after-bowling/</guid>
      <description>Just got to nextspace cause monitor went out again === have a solid 2 hours here to go completely savage on the new site. || we got a jacket yesterday for my music video, some nice blue one helen fronted 80 bucks for then we&amp;rsquo;re going to return.
Been songwriting like crazy here, analog. Definitely going to call chris about wiring me money to get this laptop fixed- I just sucks cause the repair is going to cost more than what I bought the damn thing for, but it has all working software and the right osx version that doesn&amp;rsquo;t suck complete nazi dick so I&amp;rsquo;m not racist this is my safe space || I speak and write free so you can too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baruch Atah Adunai</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/baruch-atah-adunai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:09:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/baruch-atah-adunai/</guid>
      <description>When paul&amp;rsquo;s dad was in the hospital and had a NDE (near death exp):
the entity said:
 Baruch Atah Adunai  The Indian Shaman was : Hunkpapsioux OR they are just called ThinkPapa || HunkPapa one of the 7 council of the Lacota Tribe
If humans were fish lyrics =&amp;gt; our fish tank got dead fish live fish fish that play dead! fish that dress up suits and reapers depends on her season  Hypothetically, what we do in this dimension affects higher{lower} dimensions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Rent NextDoor</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/4-rent-nextdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:01:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/4-rent-nextdoor/</guid>
      <description>1201
( Time is now )
had a great yesterday night recorded the weiner circle after a nice intimate session at Lillys for the first time with ONE BEER DRANK ONLY ONE BEER AND IT WAS THE BEST NIGHT but helen was sick so you know I had some extra energy
but got numbers from these two girls at the weiner circle it was sick &amp;mdash; we&amp;rsquo;re going to record sometime this week and they said I was going to make it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babysitting to Hyde Park Jazz Fest</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/babysitting-to-hyde-park-jazz-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 12:23:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/babysitting-to-hyde-park-jazz-fest/</guid>
      <description>1224
Transcription from legal pad # 2 =&amp;gt;
Sept 26th, just babysat Max at whole foods for an hour and a half Now helen and I are on CTA heading 4 free jazz for the rest of the day =&amp;gt; paul told me on the phone the moon landing was definitely fake and he&amp;rsquo;s not afraid of anyone anymore. Pretty woke for a high school history teacher. He said his students are dumb they think the Earth is flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Soul Whose Intentions Are Lake Plants</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/a-soul-whose-intentions-are-lake-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:24:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/a-soul-whose-intentions-are-lake-plants/</guid>
      <description>025
when you hear so much of people dying
related it to the plasted and wax paper
related to the convenience of hot n ready food
and the weirdos thinking
if it all gives you cancer don&amp;rsquo;t worry about it
i cant cure your white lady
but i cn love you in a new way
everytime
and the plastic
 // 1 day after bonjos bday // CHP chad mic copped a mirage --&amp;gt; don&#39;t even have to write nor record yet I&#39;m so happy doing both we knew concrete could work so well with lake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apathy Gains in My Sewey Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/apathy-gains-in-my-sewey-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:49:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/apathy-gains-in-my-sewey-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>*2351*
h is the best thingin this town
and she&amp;rsquo;s not in this town
like I’m underwater and my proprioception is telling me my skin is a few centimeters off of where it actually is so its lying and Im doing these things and apathy is the main underlying feeling
fire as a field bridge water as a field bridge air as a field bridge humans as a field bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And What Saved Me Today</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/and-what-saved-me-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 14:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/and-what-saved-me-today/</guid>
      <description>1457
 I&amp;rsquo;m having a good day -started a bank account it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time without one
you don&amp;rsquo;t even know the invisible pressures all around me
and you don&amp;rsquo;t even know how stubborn I am
tomorrow we&amp;rsquo;ll find out my dad if my dad has lmyphoma
my mom started the morning with a little meeting telling me I need to move out and work and make money</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikini Business Meeting</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/bikini-business-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 09:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/bikini-business-meeting/</guid>
      <description>0914
after life
you believe in it
i do then theres
until its proven or until its shown to work
-=-==-=-
2027
like why is no one
asking the right questions
umm like the kids
are asking the passwords
and the adults forgot the passwords
and I forgot the point
but Im paying off my sleep debt
just filmed with alex
in the back roads and lemon fields of more vhs poliwat shots</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BeforeAndAfter_YUPPPPPPPP Budwieser Beach Instead of Dmv Suck My T</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beforeandafter_yupppppppp-budwieser-beach-instead-of-dmv-suck-my-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 18:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beforeandafter_yupppppppp-budwieser-beach-instead-of-dmv-suck-my-t/</guid>
      <description>asddsad a
1834
To god To our creators To our endeavors To our dreams! Who are we what are we In relation too .oo too You ! Not one of these OH who am I in relation to you talks If you don&#39;t know now you&#39;l never know accurately It hurts doesn&#39;t it, letting words hurt Words never hurt they never did It&#39;s you that thought they did Words never hurt And the more words you construct The less you get from the true true And baby Aaadas He sufferes now, and 900 billion future humans will be born with access to his brain Is that not worth it Would he go against that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Living Through Chemicals</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/better-living-through-chemicals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:28:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/better-living-through-chemicals/</guid>
      <description>Freestyler&amp;rsquo;s Anonymous (FA) Callback from KZSU
  that&amp;rsquo;s what my dad said he wants to do 3 applications of roundup in the way back and ironically there were 2 commercials of the monsanto class acttion lawsuit stuff saying to call if you&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to chemicals.
so I&amp;rsquo;m not about it. hate it. hate it hate it all and everyone&amp;rsquo;s gone an dI just need to record my albums and my mood is gone .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Sad and Protein Waffles</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-sad-and-protein-waffles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 20:55:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-sad-and-protein-waffles/</guid>
      <description>2056
watching &amp;lsquo;unit 42&amp;rsquo; with dad on the couch - for the first time in a long time.
helkat and becca left town today, we had a nice 2 day stint of beaches beaches beaches vhs and fam.
Im so lonely now idk what to do, but got 2 new songs in the pipeline from the visit.
can&amp;rsquo;t do much tonight, going to recover and sleep sleep sleep and then start a new sequence with a fast tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of Us Owe</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/all-of-us-owe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 16:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/all-of-us-owe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cool Contest</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-the-cool-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 22:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-the-cool-contest/</guid>
      <description>1041pm
all my journals are getting hands
heckout rocket reach
https://twitter.com/jasnblack
||
spend 24 hours on new yorker
||
https://medium.com/s/story/how-i-fully-quit-google-and-you-can-too-4c2f3f85793a
[outline] [history] Pale Blue Dot FM’s mission is to produce open source creative tech projects, and distribute these projects through digital and physical goods and services for all humans. We want to harness the power of art and modern technology to inspire empathy, augment lived experience, and provide an open source alternative to everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Weeks of Pilots Logs Slipped Through My Fingers</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/2-weeks-of-pilots-logs-slipped-through-my-fingers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 17:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/2-weeks-of-pilots-logs-slipped-through-my-fingers/</guid>
      <description>http://utminers.utep.edu/jquintana4/about_me.htm
sat 1058 AM
last night we had matt jack marina ted brian denis helen cam all in the same spot and had a great fucking time ||
I was trying to finish the PBD site, the sequence starts in 2 days \ \ but stopped by 10 and helped jack with an 8 minute max version of the sims sims for some play competition at piano fight - the winner gets 5 grand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood on My Dick to Eating Beef Penis</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/blood-on-my-dick-to-eating-beef-penis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:42:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/blood-on-my-dick-to-eating-beef-penis/</guid>
      <description>1044pm
|| you could call this day roller coaster ||
=-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-=</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tEHES HANDS</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 03:41:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</guid>
      <description>0341pm
I AM BACK ON after
%%^&amp;**** - days out  Text secondary
Dashed Thick</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>