<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Federal Beat Reserve</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/welcome-to-the-federal-beat-reserve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/welcome-to-the-federal-beat-reserve/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Beat Reserve is the following:
 The Federal Beat Reserve is a dictionary with electronic instrumentals as the definitions. It’s name plays upon the idea that the US government might officially support the creative cataloging of music for the people. My aim is to create a non verbal sound reference for every word in language, through the action of encapsulating everything semantic into a discrete duration of instrumental music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chessy the Bus Sessions</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/chessy-the-bus-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:35:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/chessy-the-bus-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Bus Sessions by Many Humans  Producer writeup:
I was looking to record musician&amp;rsquo;s original songs that they haven&amp;rsquo;t recorded before, in a natural and impromtu setting. Most of these songs are not available elsewhere because of this.
    Also available for download @archive youtube search for the videos:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>1603
 (V Vamp) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I see right through you oh Grasshopper my Grasshopper I&#39;m balls to wall not slept at all at mall saw hole in bathroom stall yikes that&#39;s not my verse! (V1) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I speak to you in total confidence from consiquence in pool go go girl straight postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are proud most are lonely few are loud I&#39;m proud I&#39;m a prophet of my past predicated on past mistakes if I love jiminy cricket spitting to crickets my mistakes I spit to you my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I cannot work here no more x6 I know you know we know x2 So what&#39;d the grasshopper say michael my michael You in a fix you need a fix double down on that double dick  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Time I Go Out Imma Teach Got a Lesson</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 19:18:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</guid>
      <description>[chorus] next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson gotta lesson from the drunk shaman well tortured to death there&#39;s snow on his sleeve I make a plan to fuck for a living believe wouldn&#39;t you these discoveries my discoveries stop pissin on mom so next time I go out Imma leave a note pro bono bonobo in peripheral tho goa koa my homie hobo as of late they my therapy today I need it i breath it I Greg Elementary my dear watson The ABCs of Boy Love  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Lies in the Center of Github</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/what-lies-in-the-center-of-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 12:30:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/what-lies-in-the-center-of-github/</guid>
      <description>github.center.wav by Michael Betts  Artist writeup:
The philosophy behind Github has been a big inspiration as a digital media artist
Each track is a git command line, the idea being an instrumental track you can hit play on whenever you need that command.
Tracks are all free and open source, and some of the STEMS(the ones that didn&amp;rsquo;t get lost on my broken laptop) are available here @archive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you need to hear in 40 years?</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/portfolio/what-do-you-want-to-hear-in-40-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 12:40:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/portfolio/what-do-you-want-to-hear-in-40-years/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m going to need to hear in 40 years&amp;hellip;.
 A collage of all the most important friends, family, and voices of a time when I was hosting a weekly show at Stanford.
Credits: PBD Episode Creds New Episodes Every Sunday @Noon Ep 1 welcome to my sound library  
 Humans (In Order of Appearance) 
 Michael Betts, Host
 
 Enoch Cincotta(singing) and Joey Lynch as prickly pear in first song https://pricklypair.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>