<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Songs on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/song/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Songs on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 15:15:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/song/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Songbook Master List</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/songbook-master-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 19:24:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/songbook-master-list/</guid>
      <description>Songs from the the beginning of when I started writing songs, in the closest possible order I can remember, with links to them. Chords, sheet music, charts, and reference audio or video is updated often. The following are just the list of songs, just go to https://poliw.at/tags/song and then use command or control F to find the song from this list.
 ** NOTE these are just songs by definition a piece of music with words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>READ ME FIRST</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-read-me-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-read-me-first/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents  Intro P  bio beliefs big pic The POLIW.AT umbrella  Music by G  Anti-folk Piano Schizop  POLIW.AT LOVES YOU, PLU Format  Intro P  Bio  I&amp;rsquo;m poliwat, born and raised in the small town Nipomo, San Luis Obispo county. Both my parents are musicians, and I learned much about music from them. My dad worked in Owen&amp;rsquo;s Music, would repair stringed instruments, and would give lessons for periods of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Federal Beat Reserve</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/welcome-to-the-federal-beat-reserve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/welcome-to-the-federal-beat-reserve/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Beat Reserve is the following:
 The Federal Beat Reserve is a dictionary with electronic instrumentals as the definitions. It’s name plays upon the idea that the US government might officially support the creative cataloging of music for the people. My aim is to create a non verbal sound reference for every word in language, through the action of encapsulating everything semantic into a discrete duration of instrumental music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chessy the Bus Sessions</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/chessy-the-bus-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:35:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/chessy-the-bus-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Bus Sessions by Many Humans  Producer writeup:
I was looking to record musician&amp;rsquo;s original songs that they haven&amp;rsquo;t recorded before, in a natural and impromtu setting. Most of these songs are not available elsewhere because of this.
    Also available for download @archive youtube search for the videos:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is a Sacred Circle</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:21:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</guid>
      <description>  Lyrics life is a sacred circle we dance to pray we pray to heal we heal to live we live to dance life is a sacred circle   Originally recorded on the beaches of Lake Superior from Cathy Nelson, and she played her flute. This is an old prayer from the Lacota Tribe, a native people before the United States.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Piece of Man Is Work</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-a-pieve-of-man-is-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:00:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-a-pieve-of-man-is-work/</guid>
      <description>miss myself missing you - poliw.at [early release] 13:03
Freewrite #123089 &amp;lsquo;What a piece of work is man? Washing up dishes this morning plotting how to cut my dick off, I get too horny too often for this lifestyle. But it teaches patience, my current best reason to look forward to aging. Some men say it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go away. Well yeah that&amp;rsquo;s probably right, but you have more time to develop your interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember Member 18th of November</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/remember-member-18th-of-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 15:15:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/remember-member-18th-of-november/</guid>
      <description>15:15
de live mysteries de plank position tapes from under the rock with kids  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Playlist 1</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/final-playlist-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 22:25:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/final-playlist-1/</guid>
      <description>I am a spliff World my stage Grasshopper my Grasshopper Next time I got out Toe Blue If I was the butcher Constantly zoning out 3PAC 0HOOTS is dead miss myself missing you ___  piano ones:
treasures
all of us
give mommy a break give daddy a breakdown
bpm 65 F# one
bpm 85 Gmaj7 one
bpm 95 Bbmin7
bpm 107 Gmaj7 one
bpm 122 Bbmin 7 Dbmin C7 one || Bbmin7 Eb Ab7 Amaj7 Ab7 Amaj7 || C7 F7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut My Roots They Grew Back Double</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/cut-my-roots-they-grew-back-double/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 14:23:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/cut-my-roots-they-grew-back-double/</guid>
      <description>h8u9ijokl&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill Never Die This Is Why</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/ill-never-die-this-is-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 22:05:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/ill-never-die-this-is-why/</guid>
      <description>weeks since a timestamp, but writing competition therapy startx
Chapter 1 Last login: Thu Nov 14 16:53:27 on ttys000 poliwats-MacBook-Pro:~ poliwat$ poliwats-MacBook-Pro:~ poliwat$ cd Dropbox/code/poliw.at poliwats-MacBook-Pro:poliw.at poliwat$ ls archetypes	content	docs	layouts	resources	themes config.toml	data	docs2	public	static poliwats-MacBook-Pro:poliw.at poliwat$ hugo new song/ill-never-die-this-is-why.md /Users/poliwat/Dropbox/code/poliw.at/content/song/ill-never-die-this-is-why.md created poliwats-MacBook-Pro:poliw.at poliwat$ atom . poliwats-MacBook-Pro:poliw.at poliwat$ The person you loved grows that hole&#39; she said looking up from chocolate vanilla icecream in dad&#39;s hammock. She&#39;s talking to my mom, dad&#39;s oxygen tank came in today, heart vacumn beat in the backround.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want a Ball</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-want-a-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 18:40:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-want-a-ball/</guid>
      <description>capo 2-3
 lyrics:
 C Am I want a ball to toss around C Am7 like when I was small C Am like when I was small C Am7 knock knock knock C Am I live next door and every moment C Am7 I see I see uniqueness F G F G7 and I see suffering under your eyelids C Am I want a ball just to toss around C Am7 I want a ball just to toss around so lets play tags with the neighbor kids I&#39;ll hide in the trash then pop out real quick we&#39;re gonna die soon so don&#39;t be a bitch that&#39;s what life is I don&#39;t have perfect pitch  not below this line →</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I Was the Butcher</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/if-i-was-the-butcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 18:31:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/if-i-was-the-butcher/</guid>
      <description>(verse 1) if I was the butcher in love with the chicken it&#39;d be your neck I&#39;m in love with if you were the preacher (of the town) you&#39;d condemn all words and show love through your actions he died too early he died for a cause not military he died for this this this proverb this proverb from the ghetto is he right and he said if I was the butcher in love with the kebab it&#39;d be your stick I&#39;m in love with if I were the liver that saved my dad I&#39;d become a nun and show through action if I was the shaman that lived in the protest shamans at a protest signs that read genocide copyright not lives internet will not be homogenized write software that frees the world not enslaves the world  ___ not below this line → what came first chicken or the vegan or you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toe Blue</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/toe-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 18:18:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/toe-blue/</guid>
      <description>lyrics:
(verse 1) toe blue (x2-8) used your toe to tell the time tht was just timeless x2 that was just timeless that was just priceless x2 all night one night it rained toe blue we felt it (chorus 1) let that toe sail I know you you you you x2 (verse 2) lake blue (x2-8) mouths open wide I love(has teeth)x3-4 I forgot my love has teeth &amp;gt; (chorus 2) my finger goggles I see you you you you x2 (verse 3) storm blue (x2-8) used your card to have a night and that was just priceless and it was just freezing we were just dreaming we were just jumping we were just leaping (chorus 3) I shouldn&#39;t stare but you looked blue blue blue blue shouldn&#39;t stare so much but lifes to too too-too too-too toe to  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distant Hills - Winters almost over</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/distant-hills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 16:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/distant-hills/</guid>
      <description>Key: C
 distant hills soar throat brazzers throat you know how it goes when you freetyle for too long when you&#39;re sick with a chopin cough hmm ((with the barrelhouse brews they got em in the news and it break it down blue }} new benjamin never knew those benjamins walking around like a baller in my fucking lindas shorts that my mamma though getting more pussy than some cut throat ghengis khan but only with my words when I go hard go far akbar everybodys full of love and I just reflect it oh what up lifes a mirror lifes a sacred spliff when you hit it with chad and locatelli backroads holy shit I pick toad I pick though momma gave me her AA cup thinking already went pro and I contributed to method acting even though I know Im gonna crack this uh oh lets go to french festival do it again that&#39;s how mindy kailing got the vape on the fuckin office Ima go and drop this drop out tune in cop out mother fucker psycedelic though not official though turn it around we go and freestyle everybody now even though you mormon or you christian or you brother now I don&#39;t give a fuck I got friends who are rednecks now they could all fucking chill to the same tune smoke the same drugs uh ohhh like don&#39;t constrain your language everybody like law I freestyle I think it law I&#39;m fucking around with some ER inside the tiny heart is another one this house of cards 2 step 10 steps always always ahead turn it around I said like another nation so big well passionate about pangea is everybody up in the streets do ma feel ya I feel ya the bar is low the way we talk the way we are abusive with our non speaking yo damn that nobody is thinking why am I gonna die a die a cynic uh oh because I&#39;m not too smart to correct our actions through all these words that are not damn why is everyone so dumb why my russian blood make me wanna hit the rum why my body float insomnia make me not cum why I know every is a phase a chapter all through the maze and winters almost fucking over GO!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumble Night Dreams 2</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dumble-night-dreams-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 09:37:32 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dumble-night-dreams-2/</guid>
      <description>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dumble_Amplifiers
gilian welch oh me oh my oh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:38:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/test/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nurse Mic</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/nurse-mic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 08:48:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/nurse-mic/</guid>
      <description>848AM
Been real busy how many days now? Been nursing dad he&amp;rsquo;s been on hospice, can&amp;rsquo;t think straight, didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep much or well at all, laptops broken but using teddy&amp;rsquo;s old TV that has an acrylic laser cut sign of robin on it. Just updating this ipod so I can keep nursing well with new tunes. H kissed me back barely and felt sexually dead, she went to starbucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another One Flies West</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/another-one-flies-west/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/another-one-flies-west/</guid>
      <description>2132 || Been offline never got to get this screen fixed but setup with ted&amp;rsquo;s monitor in the room . been sleeping next to dad since flying back, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s been seven days now. yeah about that really. this is the hardest period of my life. || dads in the hospice bed and I&amp;rsquo;ve been recording every day; people visiting, mom and I taking care of him, music, the nurses, bonnie and her two daughters, phone calls, voicemails, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PaintedOnRoof MetConstantineAndSlum</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/paintedonroof-metconstantineandslum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 20:21:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/paintedonroof-metconstantineandslum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If My Dads Going Down From Cancer Ill Write a Rock Opera</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/if-my-dads-going-down-from-cancer-ill-write-a-rock-opera/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 10:55:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/if-my-dads-going-down-from-cancer-ill-write-a-rock-opera/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I in Love or Am I Obsessed</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/am-i-in-love-or-am-i-obsessed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 22:10:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/am-i-in-love-or-am-i-obsessed/</guid>
      <description>am I in love or am I obsessed im all in on her olive shes out two hours Im obsessing my hearts arrest without convitction my hearts arrest accused and not guilty she leave 2 hours its rough and when she finally walks through I&#39;ll hate her and (sub snuff her /sub) that&#39;s that that&#39;s love that&#39;s love and that&#39;s that so am I obsessed or am I in love whats the difference when its reciprocated  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggs Paint and a Womens Talk</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/eggs-paint-and-a-womens-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 09:50:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/eggs-paint-and-a-womens-talk/</guid>
      <description>and I didn&amp;rsquo;t finished the though because I focused on the good word:
this site is all moving to musical cues :
{play your favorite song}
Bonnie:
tired and alone if alone was you  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BWall Death of Pauls Hookahs</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/bwall-death-of-pauls-hookahs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/bwall-death-of-pauls-hookahs/</guid>
      <description>painted all day had mugs pizza first time deep dish pep AMAZING
mace practice in the driveway after work and then always sunny, south park, and {{typing put put gold}} :) .
12:13AM
 it&#39;s brick wall bwall hookahs are the shoe brand made for tennis she hated painted all day sacrificed them at a rate constant and look at what you can achieve&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;((archive))&amp;lt;/sub&amp;gt; by not feeding your soul not subscribing to your face mole your face mole that says me what the good word told you and growing grown gone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mace Practice Breakin Night</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/mace-practice-breakin-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/mace-practice-breakin-night/</guid>
      <description>1026
forgot all the good good lyrics of yesterday and maybe cause they weren&amp;rsquo;t
Someone threw a rock into the studio window last night at (eagle)aka hb but we weren&amp;rsquo;t there. We were sleeping in the haunted room max sees ghosts. We only heard some weird noises and then someone whispered to just me but Helen didn&amp;rsquo;t hear it. Slept like a rock despite all this and we slept in till 10, have another long day working, I&amp;rsquo;ll be painting in an hour or 2 and papa is making us eggs right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arp Hats the Machine Makes</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/arp-hats-the-machine-makes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 10:34:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/arp-hats-the-machine-makes/</guid>
      <description>1034AM
just got to nextspace going to work on poliw.at || need a workout there&amp;rsquo;s a gym pass in my bag - studios not free until 2:30 - 3:00
got filmed last night pap andre emma came over and it was a real fun night, did the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Year Old Said GodisFake Then We Ate Two Whole Ducks After Bowling</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/4-year-old-said-godisfake-then-we-ate-two-whole-ducks-after-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 14:28:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/4-year-old-said-godisfake-then-we-ate-two-whole-ducks-after-bowling/</guid>
      <description>Just got to nextspace cause monitor went out again === have a solid 2 hours here to go completely savage on the new site. || we got a jacket yesterday for my music video, some nice blue one helen fronted 80 bucks for then we&amp;rsquo;re going to return.
Been songwriting like crazy here, analog. Definitely going to call chris about wiring me money to get this laptop fixed- I just sucks cause the repair is going to cost more than what I bought the damn thing for, but it has all working software and the right osx version that doesn&amp;rsquo;t suck complete nazi dick so I&amp;rsquo;m not racist this is my safe space || I speak and write free so you can too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collage Genre Before F Pasta</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/collage-genre-before-f-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 22:08:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/collage-genre-before-f-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Making pasta forgot what I was originally going to write to start this but it was a lot more important than making pasta
listening to bob dylan in 1075 and yeah I agree with my dad he sucks so I have high hopes I suck at singing but can write a song as if it&amp;rsquo;s taking a piss so we&amp;rsquo;re in good company America || so no jokes aside had a great day with helen we rode divvys and saw david shileds twice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Whaling Erotica</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/on-whaling-erotica/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:27:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/on-whaling-erotica/</guid>
      <description> poem for helen on whaling erotica
 helen in your exes room allow or better yet that dining table is stable soon let our utensils be our harpoons sharp our choice of words savage erotic while impulsive our hands dictators of our choice of words cause savages are slaves to their hands pigs are slaves to their minds we’ll get out of this alive is my thought or lie lie down rest remain prone gives you back massage fuck till dawn dawn to dusk dusk to rash rough seas be the woman in thee my woman to be helen of joy  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theres a Trumpet Thats Ablazing</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/theres-a-trumpet-thats-ablazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:23:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/theres-a-trumpet-thats-ablazing/</guid>
      <description> Lyrics: there’s a trumpet this a blazing and its calling out m name last night but I don’t remember it last night but it was something about my brother and something about my lover both related somehow realize, realize there’s pain in the oh oh ohoha ocean pain in the oh oh ohoha ocean just winding up an escher staircase that’s totally infinite and I know that you are feeling kinda frustrated and I know that you got some time I got some time to sometime some time to sometime to sometimes I got sometime I got too much time to think sometime I got too much time to think sometimes I been meeting your exes checking they yz s feeling  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Out for Cigs</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/media-out-for-cigs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:20:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/media-out-for-cigs/</guid>
      <description>lyrics: independent platform ||capitalizing on the longform ||technological transformation possibility of dialogue|| End of capital the verb lack of interference unmediated media you can’t misrepresent people anymore its okay miles you’re parents have agreed to become zombies so that you can think indecently the weight of nothing() and everything lies on your shoulders people hear what the see so don&#39;t talk about what you can show and you’ll feel so much better when you have money thats what they all say but will I still think clearly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dont Talk What You Can Show</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dont-talk-what-you-can-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:16:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dont-talk-what-you-can-show/</guid>
      <description>lryics: use needs to take all the power to give it just give it back song called don’t add words to this song called just let it play  99’ comedy CD and she lied about the bits and his perspective she changed the bits to make them misogynist and there was no recourse  =-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-=
The power with the person with the pen || the typewriter
=-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-==-=-=-=
I don’t do interviews anymore you wanna know about me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marathon Moleskin MMBV</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/marathon-moleskin-mmbv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 10:24:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/marathon-moleskin-mmbv/</guid>
      <description>1024
colectivo catchup before work yea yea
big alien alf fable  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Oven on Whose Outside</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/is-the-oven-on-whose-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 14:04:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/is-the-oven-on-whose-outside/</guid>
      <description>ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok opk ok ok ok ok ok hugo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Push or to Stretch It Out Further</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/to-push-or-to-stretch-it-out-further/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:22:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/to-push-or-to-stretch-it-out-further/</guid>
      <description>should I push what I know or stretch it out farther
like stay up all night by the lake
just to see the light a minute
worth the 12 hours
she doesn&amp;rsquo;t know
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to explain it
but it&amp;rsquo;s worth it
every time
and
every fucking time
whter it&amp;rsquo;s overwhleming
or something beyond me
yeah it&amp;rsquo;s a bad tip beyond repairing
but also something tht no one ever knew</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Therefore</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/therefore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:15:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/therefore/</guid>
      <description>SDASHDjk smooth
if the wright brothers were left handed therefore I&#39;m right  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Then There Was Fire Ass Pixels</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/and-then-there-was-fire-ass-pixels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/and-then-there-was-fire-ass-pixels/</guid>
      <description>2109
Never drank in a whole foods
so its fitting first time you get drunk then tpy 200 words
a minute it feels plans out the window
80 words a minute it is
but feels 200 plus 3 tips
and an open card means I&amp;rsquo;m leaving happy
and my money isn&amp;rsquo;t anything
doesn&amp;rsquo;t meant anything
is nothing
in the land of the rich
and the free
until dont&amp;rsquo; have any</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surfing in the Sea</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/surfing-in-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:45:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/surfing-in-the-sea/</guid>
      <description>D C D ( capo 0 or 2(depending on health) ) (Verse 1) I was just surfing in the sea hoping you were wathing me on a bright summers day day day gay gay gay gay gay gay gay gay gay day (Chorus 1) and a shark came swimming right outa the oceans floor and she said that looks like a big juicy wet seal to me uh oh (Verse 2) well I was dead right there I forgot my shark repellant spray though I struggle with my belief in god I began to pray pray pray pray pray pray pray pray pray pray pray pray (Chorus 2) The shark came swimming and made an awesome roar made an awesome roar I swear I never heard anything like it before and it went like This (meow solo vocals GLHF) my reprise(mine) but it was you who saved me though I still long to break free I asked you how you made that shark go you replied you did not know your zodiac is an aquarius and you just go with the flow flow flow flow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow flow (verse 3) so I went and gave you a big wet kiss but bad breath came on mighty fast I swear I nearly drowned (chorus 3) but I said screw it you&#39;re my love so I gave you the biggest wettest kiss around (bridge 3) cause it was you who saved me although I still long to break free  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Was Wandering in My Head</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-was-wandering-in-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:35:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-was-wandering-in-my-head/</guid>
      <description> capo 4 (waking up G and more, listen to it)
 (verse 1) I was wandering in my head even though I&#39;m tired tired you came wandering like a Pokemon you would always lie high in the grass just like a lazy Snorlax z z z you could be a Butterfree (verse 2) you came a running cause there was a spider all up in your face face I latched on quick like a Bulbasaur now we are face to face (reprise) ho ho ho ho kisses are wet ho ho ho ho kisses fucking sting (bridge) the moment you get outa that existential funk the moment you stop seeing that punk (build up fast part) (( all a big &amp;gt; )) we can and we can talk and have a platonic relationship in the back of my bus cause everything is cool and everything is great when we live in a world where no one master bates and if you go to church and compartmentalize your life and do what your told and your told to be a wife the rich are getting richer and the poor always want more so lets just pop some molly and hit the dance floor (verse 3) fee fie foe fum here comes my girlfriend and I think she&#39;s mad at me there&#39;s diminishing returns on apologies so I say sorry strategically but ho ho ho ho kisses are wet ho ho ho ho kisses fucking sting  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seize the Day Girl</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/seize-the-day-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:14:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/seize-the-day-girl/</guid>
      <description>lyrics
 You want to play some sudohku I only want to connect the dots you talking to me about getting old whens your birthday I forgot shut up and seize te day girl cause theres way cooler things than a guy with a guitar I  &amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;new rule you can&amp;rsquo;t listen to freestyles while we&amp;rsquo;re walking&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;
LOL no I didn&amp;rsquo;t stand for that
it calms me down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Talking Smiling Keeping</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/walking-talking-smiling-keeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:08:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/walking-talking-smiling-keeping/</guid>
      <description>lyrics and chords
 walking talking smiling keeping things close to my chest you can always lie on my chest wen you&#39;re feeling stressed when you&#39;re feeling blessed but london bridges london bridges but london bridges fall london bridges london bridges london bridges fall (breakdown) shaving legs and I sense change cause you don&#39;t shave your legs nearly as much as you used to and seasons change and you look great but don&#39;t rely just on your looks girl cause that is lame oh and we go and play twister in the middle of the night and after 3 or 4 beers we&#39;re having a fight cause you want to play some monopoly but be with my girl I&#39;ll monopolize your pussy (surprise) I come in late at night you look stunning when the lights when the lights aren&#39;t so bright one step two grab myself a drink while you are watching tv and there&#39;s a man on the scren and he&#39;s telling me things I should eat and also medication so I can digest thoes things but is that man on the screen gonna fix what&#39;s between you you you you and me (whisper) and me so fuck it go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Down Central Park</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/walking-down-central-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 19:39:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/walking-down-central-park/</guid>
      <description>1939
(Verse 1) G C D Walking down central park and oh it&#39;s mighty dark please don&#39;t hurt me bum you can have all my money just don&#39;t take any of my precious pride and gum cause I got a date tonight oh with one hell of a site best I&#39;ve done in a while I care to admit with a pretty face and even better smile (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die (Verse 2) G C D I&#39;m ex military too I lied and said told that bum with a karate kick too the head then a sideways judo chop on his knee Can&#39;t fight just what I saw from MTV (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die (Verse 3) G C D Well that&#39;s the story enough&#39; said Now it&#39;s time to tuck you in bed Time to sleep this songs done and that&#39;s the story of how I met your mum (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baruch Atah Adunai</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/baruch-atah-adunai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:09:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/baruch-atah-adunai/</guid>
      <description>When paul&amp;rsquo;s dad was in the hospital and had a NDE (near death exp):
the entity said:
 Baruch Atah Adunai  The Indian Shaman was : Hunkpapsioux OR they are just called ThinkPapa || HunkPapa one of the 7 council of the Lacota Tribe
If humans were fish lyrics =&amp;gt; our fish tank got dead fish live fish fish that play dead! fish that dress up suits and reapers depends on her season  Hypothetically, what we do in this dimension affects higher{lower} dimensions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Rent NextDoor</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/4-rent-nextdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 12:01:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/4-rent-nextdoor/</guid>
      <description>1201
( Time is now )
had a great yesterday night recorded the weiner circle after a nice intimate session at Lillys for the first time with ONE BEER DRANK ONLY ONE BEER AND IT WAS THE BEST NIGHT but helen was sick so you know I had some extra energy
but got numbers from these two girls at the weiner circle it was sick &amp;mdash; we&amp;rsquo;re going to record sometime this week and they said I was going to make it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lincoln Park Bunnies Dont Know Whats in the Lake</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/lincoln-park-bunnies-dont-know-whats-in-the-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 10:42:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/lincoln-park-bunnies-dont-know-whats-in-the-lake/</guid>
      <description>1042AM
@nextdoor with hellcat - we got a solid 30 minutes before we gotta go work for the day it&amp;rsquo;s real luck- got a grapefruit an apple a yogurt and kombucha so share it&amp;rsquo;s GREAT fell asleep real sad I didn&amp;rsquo;t run out in the rain cause she was too sick to but I&amp;rsquo;m over it now - just next time it rains I&amp;rsquo;m aiming to get soaked in a tshirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books as Monopods</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/books-as-monopods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 22:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/books-as-monopods/</guid>
      <description>lyrics; I use I use I use I use books as monopods they my monopods thats why my tunes got pops I learned to love them unconditional why ever since high school my idea of love was loving the weakness then maybe that&#39;s a little Leutenant Dan in me even if you missing legs and my fingers missing girls and my girls missing fingers and I know I will say anything just to feel this and to steal it away that&#39;s the moment today notha fucking hotel indoor bathroom window aye aye thats all you need for some therapy thats what I learned from motha fuckin symphonies that are silent not a single word though that&#39;s the fucking point that&#39;s why I listen though hm there&#39;s always time to shut the fuck up when you screaming on the inside its hard to keep it in oh what up Imma mother fuckin break it down I never slow down I never throw out even without a paddle now and I&#39;m still kicking rowing everybodys throwing stones I don&#39;t fucking feel it OH no drama that&#39;s a fucking joke yeah turn around I&#39;m sharper than a cutco and you know this composer time is fucking with the past and the present and the future in the same fucking context damn then I go and change it every fuckin few moments that&#39;s why I go fast (holy shit) that&#39;s why I need a lot of fucking friends I gotta lotta love to give and not a lot ways to and a lot of ways to express it this is fucking spring street I will fucking drive them downtown when I would feed needa needa a escape up in high school today I talkin act before I fucking ditched yesterday bonnie said psychedelics ruined my life mom said I used to be so fucking nice till went to santa cruz {lindsey called it lindsey called it lindsey called it} &amp;gt; santa booz and you know that I went hard (V2) but the friends and the skills acquired easily worth the cost I&#39;d do it ten times over it if hell freezes over non apathetic I take the cost damn dead it&#39;s priceless every single moment reprogram your brain then when you fuckin hate this subject yourself to fuckin challenge everyday get addicted to it I&#39;m not afflicted to it throw me in the coffin 7 days I won&#39;t lose my fucking mind today what kind of teacher and preacher could&#39;ve fucking preach that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future a Fake Video for Everything</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/the-future-a-fake-video-for-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 22:15:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/the-future-a-fake-video-for-everything/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tithes for Tony</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/tithes-for-tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:54:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/tithes-for-tony/</guid>
      <description>2154
Had a great day of work for Aris
when I did the transfer from the blue line to the brown I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like quite going home yet. I walked around looking for a nice sounding ambient place to record brown dog. It was only 8 pm and only chains and nice restaurants were open. Nothing I liked. I somehow walked straight to the next CTA station, and yet again gave someone a smile and they asked for money, anyone you smile at in the city is looking for money so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Dog Heads to Chicago</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/brown-dog-heads-to-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:16:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/brown-dog-heads-to-chicago/</guid>
      <description>1416
The following are transcriptions from free legal pads :
 1 day after Bonjo&#39;s Bday CHP chad mic copped a mirage 8 months unregistered never got caught Thank you for letting me freestyle If I freestyle Dub bitch as is motif and hook and all as is hurt dumb bitches hurt dumb bitches I call it as I see it who&#39;e counting anymore 3 months ago I wrote thank God for like why am I even here at this coffeeshop pissed but not before not hurt but hurt but not &#39;way before&#39; written too many times this dude doing database queries smells worse than me I know ause I just smelled myself oh wow the freewrite is over today is recording, last night was recording Andre&#39;s acapella shorts while helen was venmoing ollie 40 bucks for drinks and or food =&amp;gt; her gmail was logged in on my phone &amp;quot;don&#39;t want my name on a basketball&amp;quot; chain and ball 1 lyft 1 uber and I&#39;m douple||triple peed =&amp;gt; patient pissed peeboy who knows why am I sitting here cause seeing her even though I&#39;m triple pee is better than not seeing her =&amp;gt; and today 4 sure is not the day for it But bumping 30 minute freewrite back when I was driving Locatelli&#39;s corolla  Don&#39;t even have to write nor record yet so happy I&#39;m doing both who knew conrete could work so well with lake and looking up at the sky with my finger goggles I though this is way too beautiful for you to not be here Though I&#39;m sure some atrium at Emma&#39;s work would compliment the clouds but here at the lake my ankles spashing carelessly, you can see the currents underwater the deadly rip tows and every good sailor knows looking up at the winds in the clouds is how you can see the currents below I the arrogant swimmer don&#39;t question I suppose up the currents underwater are inline with the wind in the clouds pushing 30 miles an hour thousands of feet above me and the musicians only job is to document capture destroy manipulate over think convolute rule over forget about justify nothing with logic as church no stop - just look up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operation Brown Dog Day 2</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/operation-brown-dog-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 13:00:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/operation-brown-dog-day-2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>1603
 (V Vamp) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I see right through you oh Grasshopper my Grasshopper I&#39;m balls to wall not slept at all at mall saw hole in bathroom stall yikes that&#39;s not my verse! (V1) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I speak to you in total confidence from consiquence in pool go go girl straight postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are proud most are lonely few are loud I&#39;m proud I&#39;m a prophet of my past predicated on past mistakes if I love jiminy cricket spitting to crickets my mistakes I spit to you my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I cannot work here no more x6 I know you know we know x2 So what&#39;d the grasshopper say michael my michael You in a fix you need a fix double down on that double dick  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terry Rash Wanton</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/terry-rash-wanton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 15:33:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/terry-rash-wanton/</guid>
      <description>do you lose respect for me if I bate right now or gain respect
so I dont bug you
cause its been an hour since we had sex
and I can&amp;rsquo;t hold it
that&amp;rsquo;s why I don&amp;rsquo;t go out by myself
 cause now hours later we&#39;re getting back to our roots just biked to you and we&#39;re starting our night at Volumes Books in Wicker Park I brought us a bottle of Cali Roots and plastic cups we&#39;ll open the bottle with this pen and I&#39;ll get back to writing about my hate of plastic but the plastic in me loves plastic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are a Wonderful Person</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/you-are-a-wonderful-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 16:45:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/you-are-a-wonderful-person/</guid>
      <description>you are a wonderful person too complex a creature to be nailed down on any one person place or thing besides maybe you&#39;ve got the same curse as me patiently waiting for the freedom working towards the freedom of diner hopping going from diner to diner to diner to diner.  Cause when you get to one, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter it it&amp;rsquo;s a desert outside, a busy street, or snowing. Diners stay timeless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Time I Go Out Imma Teach Got a Lesson</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 19:18:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</guid>
      <description>[chorus] next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson gotta lesson from the drunk shaman well tortured to death there&#39;s snow on his sleeve I make a plan to fuck for a living believe wouldn&#39;t you these discoveries my discoveries stop pissin on mom so next time I go out Imma leave a note pro bono bonobo in peripheral tho goa koa my homie hobo as of late they my therapy today I need it i breath it I Greg Elementary my dear watson The ABCs of Boy Love  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too Many Pics</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/too-many-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 16:15:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/too-many-pics/</guid>
      <description>the inky only helps my psyche. I&amp;rsquo;m jogging this much I feel. Lovae as capital. Hypothetical house. Pable blue dot fm. Life the musical. Federal beat reserve. What idea is going to get me 3 meals and a cot, a place to record, a beach house for my mom? Everything else will go to pilot&amp;rsquo;s license and the nonprofit turned summer camps music camp orrphange. You know. Brining back the musician in everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babysitting to Hyde Park Jazz Fest</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/babysitting-to-hyde-park-jazz-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 12:23:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/babysitting-to-hyde-park-jazz-fest/</guid>
      <description>1224
Transcription from legal pad # 2 =&amp;gt;
Sept 26th, just babysat Max at whole foods for an hour and a half Now helen and I are on CTA heading 4 free jazz for the rest of the day =&amp;gt; paul told me on the phone the moon landing was definitely fake and he&amp;rsquo;s not afraid of anyone anymore. Pretty woke for a high school history teacher. He said his students are dumb they think the Earth is flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Lies in the Center of Github</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-lies-in-the-center-of-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 12:30:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-lies-in-the-center-of-github/</guid>
      <description>github.center.wav by Michael Betts  Artist writeup:
The philosophy behind Github has been a big inspiration as a digital media artist
Each track is a git command line, the idea being an instrumental track you can hit play on whenever you need that command.
Tracks are all free and open source, and some of the STEMS(the ones that didn&amp;rsquo;t get lost on my broken laptop) are available here @archive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor in MonitorOUT</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/monitor-in-monitorout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 11:31:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/monitor-in-monitorout/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Soul Whose Intentions Are Lake Plants</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/a-soul-whose-intentions-are-lake-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:24:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/a-soul-whose-intentions-are-lake-plants/</guid>
      <description>025
when you hear so much of people dying
related it to the plasted and wax paper
related to the convenience of hot n ready food
and the weirdos thinking
if it all gives you cancer don&amp;rsquo;t worry about it
i cant cure your white lady
but i cn love you in a new way
everytime
and the plastic
 // 1 day after bonjos bday // CHP chad mic copped a mirage --&amp;gt; don&#39;t even have to write nor record yet I&#39;m so happy doing both we knew concrete could work so well with lake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Conrete Lake</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/daily-conrete-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:38:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/daily-conrete-lake/</guid>
      <description>&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;Alcohol doesn&amp;rsquo;t console&amp;rsquo; She wrote. &amp;lsquo;All is replaces is the lack of God.&amp;rsquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;margot from bluets
 Nina Simone below
 Love me leave me or leave me alone. I listened to all of you. You&#39;re speech as if the thoughtful songs of Nina Simone, thoughtful thot I thought. &amp;quot;What&#39;s this?&amp;quot; Hh asked. It&#39;s a black underarmor top, extra small and shrunk from the dryer. &amp;quot;That&#39;s my Equinox top, you gotta workout like a slut there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Irish Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/my-new-irish-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:34:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/my-new-irish-sing-along/</guid>
      <description> lyrics your youth drink but 1000 times let us clink our drinks tonight my soul your soul your soul mine! share dare stare drink all the wine!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wash Your Acapella</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/wash-your-acapella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:20:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/wash-your-acapella/</guid>
      <description>#lyrics
(verse 1) Himalayas sit down meditate ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 2) At work bathroom stall sit down take a piss ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 3) get a text she met her ex sit down ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 5) Now she home give kiss stab back ((wash your dick dick dick wash your knife)) x2 (verse 6) Dig hole what she wanted pray to God ((wash your dick dick dick watch your back)) x2 (verse 7) it was a dream she still alive thank god ((and wash her clit clit clit wash her clit )) x2 (verse 8) me on a rock in spacew kill the snakes [and] ((wash your mind mind mind wash your mind)) x4  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Never Judge Me at the Wrong Time</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/they-never-judge-me-at-the-wrong-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 10:08:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/they-never-judge-me-at-the-wrong-time/</guid>
      <description>1009
&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;I tell her don&#39;t take me out in public&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; sometimes on those days, most days, where most of the overheard conversations I hear while working, writing, broke, thinking about that one improv show that wasn&#39;t funny at all but then the comedian asked if anyone has done acid and I was recording in the front row niece&#39;s sock on my microphone and I said &#39;if you&#39;ve taken acid over 100 times are you always on acid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got That LondonGF</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/got-that-londongf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 09:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/got-that-londongf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Days</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/chicago-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 09:45:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/chicago-days/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you need to hear in 40 years?</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-do-you-want-to-hear-in-40-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 12:40:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-do-you-want-to-hear-in-40-years/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m going to need to hear in 40 years&amp;hellip;.
 A collage of all the most important friends, family, and voices of a time when I was hosting a weekly show at Stanford.
Credits: PBD Episode Creds New Episodes Every Sunday @Noon Ep 1 welcome to my sound library  
 Humans (In Order of Appearance) 
 Michael Betts, Host
 
 Enoch Cincotta(singing) and Joey Lynch as prickly pear in first song https://pricklypair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Is Written About Me</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/nothing-is-written-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 17:47:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/nothing-is-written-about-me/</guid>
      <description>Info Live Radio Excerpt at Stanford, summer 2k18, Summer Episode on Death! Long form and raw with all mistakes and magic.
  1748
Nothing is written
from larwence of arabia
and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the film before
and don&amp;rsquo;t remember that part
cause I watched it ill
like I am now
and I say ill instead of sick
=&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;= =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;=
yeah yeah yeah my brain&amp;rsquo;s in a fog and thebest writings lately I&amp;rsquo;ve done have beeeeen waaaaayyy far away from poliwa/t so far its boootiliciousful</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthier Choices</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/healthier-choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:26:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/healthier-choices/</guid>
      <description>PBD ep 2 Ep2 What are you trying to do before you die 
 Pale Blue Dawt!
or paleblue.fm (couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford keeping another website online)
 
 
 Humans (In Order of Appearance)
 
 Michael Betts  
 Reineer  
 Nick Kush, @kushberryjams 
 Sean Keilan, the Provost of Porter College and Professor of Literature. 
 //( random person private property )</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering What I Learned</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/remembering-what-i-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 13:44:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/remembering-what-i-learned/</guid>
      <description>FBR therapy Instrumental, one export with drums another export without
   ^^ When your body and mind fails, what do your hands do? It&amp;rsquo;s a good meditation. You can train your hands to work when the rest of you fails, that&amp;rsquo;s how you can play harder during the difficult times.
 1344
really remembering what I learned now
ok ok
powerade
going to apply to Uni&amp;rsquo;s
Statement of Purpose</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Stage 4 Melanoma Nipomo</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/midnight-stage-4-melanoma-nipomo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 19:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/midnight-stage-4-melanoma-nipomo/</guid>
      <description>2 days in the future
AND HE&amp;rsquo;S EATING AWAY THE FOOD THAT GAVE HIM CANCER
ON THE MEDS THAT GAVE HIM cancer
and I&amp;rsquo;m writing about how absurd it is on the machine that&amp;rsquo;s liable to give me cancer
I&amp;rsquo;m not addicted it&amp;rsquo;s a human right to communicate with machines.
1947 chad&amp;rsquo;s over
he&amp;rsquo;s editing for a wedding client
the sequence begins &amp;hellip;. NOW
dad&amp;rsquo;s dying
I&amp;rsquo;m lost
in one stage many stage of grief at the same time ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hop1 MIDNIGHT MelanomaNipomoasdsadnjfFUCKAKSma</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/hop1-midnight-melanomanipomoasdsadnjffuckaksma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 19:35:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/hop1-midnight-melanomanipomoasdsadnjffuckaksma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is in My Heart</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-is-in-my-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 19:27:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-is-in-my-heart/</guid>
      <description>Old interview video I made for a remote programming job&amp;hellip; I got it but it was only 400 a month for 20+ hours a week so I had to decline!
  sat 733pm
been writing in other places.
but tonight is the night I&amp;rsquo;ll write here.
I&amp;rsquo;m livid. I&amp;rsquo;m beyond livid. I&amp;rsquo;m so angry at everyone yet just realized only angry with myself
at least bonnie had a successful birth today, and I hope they name the child Nika.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Stories Through Acronyms</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/short-stories-through-acronyms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 09:33:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/short-stories-through-acronyms/</guid>
      <description>933am
wow life
i am now a short sorty a walking short story my whole life a short story
my whole life a very short story
therapy begins
people write man I write and god laughs
its not man plans god laughs
its I write god laughs
with me
I laugh with god
even in the gutter
is how stubborn you can carry
so no its not throwing the baby out with</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Orient</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/how-do-you-orient/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 21:12:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/how-do-you-orient/</guid>
      <description>  aka kek
skele master doc for my sake engrain and iterate pray my words fruitful and my actions not deceitful no worries in my heart when my drink&#39;s full   hop = QT
 skip = IRL
 jump = PBD
 drop = FBR
 L = HH
 Cooz = FA
 Friends = FRI||migo||MIGO||
 no rules/bloopers/lore/credz like a buoy (hooksOfTheFuture) ___   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moon Out Wolf Out of COURSE BlueDressredShoes</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/moon-out-wolf-out-of-course-bluedressredshoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 20:56:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/moon-out-wolf-out-of-course-bluedressredshoes/</guid>
      <description>2111
og ok of course the device with the most potential to free us enslaves us at first we don&#39;t have the social structure fortitude set yet there are no platos of the phone there are none yet who speaks and performs actions in a healthy way with the phone ? no one I know and I&#39;m one of the saviest of my friends and only the rich maybe probably well I&#39;m not going home just yet cause its a full moon it mightve been last night but I&#39;m a man I&#39;m emotionally behind at least 24 hours on some things all the time yet ahead of time my dad finds out how far the cancer has spread and the tears I shed with a smile the tears just fall through these actions with power tools through these actions with paint that&#39;s not lead based but probably has something in it equally as toxic and my bare hands feel it and my nose smells it I saw about 7 years ago now the cancer in my dad and tomorrow he&#39;ll know so yeah I&#39;m emotionally ahead when I live for the humans that don&#39;t exist yet all my work always free is what frees me my religion more women in ppower and I can&#39;t go home if I want to be a respectable wolf cause it&#39;s my parent&#39;s 32 anniversay that&#39;s longer than I&#39;ve been alive so tonight&#39;s their night getting picked up for AA @ 630 oo way to go future mic !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Moneys Gonna Change Them and I Aint Got Any</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/only-moneys-gonna-change-them-and-i-aint-got-any/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 23:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/only-moneys-gonna-change-them-and-i-aint-got-any/</guid>
      <description>2317
but Im working late tonight just bounced 2 ableton sessions
and got a trader joes salad
and veggies all the way
is all I ddddd ever want
00005
()(()()()()()(()transcriptioon old freestyle @ c3 this past month))
 he was sellin crack I was rollin cigs san francisco yeah (x2)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Im Christian Now NWord</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/im-christian-now-nword/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 22:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/im-christian-now-nword/</guid>
      <description>2213
what? had a great day! tore apart the ugly hutch I should&amp;rsquo;ve burned long ago in the garage studio - took inventory of scrap wood - going to hit it hard tomorrow building shelf city in the studio to be the ultimate recording oasis, then will record a bunch of songs in the last week of the month or next week or so - had a great great great time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninvited From Bible Study Cause of My Words</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/uninvited-from-bible-study-cause-of-my-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/uninvited-from-bible-study-cause-of-my-words/</guid>
      <description>0012
BS was going down at 530 and my mom and sister went and I was silently not invited back and later my mom said it was good I didn&amp;rsquo;t go and that she thinks the devil got me and she laughed and I just want to kill myself cause although I told my sister last week satan&amp;rsquo;s most brilliant invention was the &amp;lsquo;word of God&amp;rsquo; - I still get spiritual guidance through bible study and the community is nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dads Dying of Mela Lymphoma Moms Yelling at Me Im Still Sober</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dads-dying-of-mela-lymphoma-moms-yelling-at-me-im-still-sober/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 12:32:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dads-dying-of-mela-lymphoma-moms-yelling-at-me-im-still-sober/</guid>
      <description>1232
but I&amp;rsquo;m still eating cancer, I just noticed even carl&amp;rsquo;s JR has prop 65 &amp;ndash; wild
but I had a coupon greig gave me for a free famous star and I wanted to try their beyond meat thing and I needed to leave the house cause it&amp;rsquo;s bad vibes and I know I messed up I left a mess but I&amp;rsquo;ve been depressed and non op and just trying to build healthy habits and my mom is so stressed she ripped me a new one and says I&amp;rsquo;m walking all over her and I just kept telling her I&amp;rsquo;ll give her a massage right there lets just calm down she&amp;rsquo;s too stressed to think clearly and it&amp;rsquo;s stressful being around someone perpetually stressed having 1 way conversations with you and then dad&amp;rsquo;s dying of cancer now so I just don&amp;rsquo;t even know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loose Ends 50 Steps Ahead Rehab D8ish</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/loose-ends-50-steps-ahead-rehab-d8ish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/loose-ends-50-steps-ahead-rehab-d8ish/</guid>
      <description>0035
fuck this month is only about mental physical spiritual health n growth
and fuck my work
when it&amp;rsquo;s been only the death of me
and I still get stuff done
and got 50 gigs of converterd vhs tapes today
and started fresh edit on cuz brian&amp;rsquo;s keys and poetry he sent
and edited 3 pac 0 hoots is dead more it&amp;rsquo;s almost ready for spotify as possibly a single</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apathy Gains in My Sewey Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/apathy-gains-in-my-sewey-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:49:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/apathy-gains-in-my-sewey-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>*2351*
h is the best thingin this town
and she&amp;rsquo;s not in this town
like I’m underwater and my proprioception is telling me my skin is a few centimeters off of where it actually is so its lying and Im doing these things and apathy is the main underlying feeling
fire as a field bridge water as a field bridge air as a field bridge humans as a field bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And What Saved Me Today</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/and-what-saved-me-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 14:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/and-what-saved-me-today/</guid>
      <description>1457
 I&amp;rsquo;m having a good day -started a bank account it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time without one
you don&amp;rsquo;t even know the invisible pressures all around me
and you don&amp;rsquo;t even know how stubborn I am
tomorrow we&amp;rsquo;ll find out my dad if my dad has lmyphoma
my mom started the morning with a little meeting telling me I need to move out and work and make money</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikini Business Meeting</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/bikini-business-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 09:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/bikini-business-meeting/</guid>
      <description>0914
after life
you believe in it
i do then theres
until its proven or until its shown to work
-=-==-=-
2027
like why is no one
asking the right questions
umm like the kids
are asking the passwords
and the adults forgot the passwords
and I forgot the point
but Im paying off my sleep debt
just filmed with alex
in the back roads and lemon fields of more vhs poliwat shots</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steppenwolf With Mom</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/steppenwolf-with-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 22:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/steppenwolf-with-mom/</guid>
      <description>2234
beccas in puerto rico for a wedding
working for brian tomorrow morning
and calling pastor archie telling him I can&amp;rsquo;t make it to church cause of it and I can fix his sound box thing sometime in the week
all my life could fit in a box I miss myself missing you my laptop missing a screw all I owe could fit in a box I miss myself missing you my laptop missing a screw all my time could fit in a box I miss myself missing you my laptop missing a screw  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SobD2 Filmed Alex as Poliwat Now Recording at C3</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/sobd2-filmed-alex-as-poliwat-now-recording-at-c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 21:02:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/sobd2-filmed-alex-as-poliwat-now-recording-at-c3/</guid>
      <description>2103
Verse 1 ``` God&amp;hellip;suck my dick Lennon got shot for less than this true power of friends freestyler&amp;rsquo;s anonymous for the lyrically afflicted flow addicted my girls in Greece so ex&amp;rsquo;s nudies got new meaning
William Blake on the track cause Jesus gave me crack ````
chris im the og the og the im the og og og og og og og og og</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BeforeAndAfter_YUPPPPPPPP Budwieser Beach Instead of Dmv Suck My T</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beforeandafter_yupppppppp-budwieser-beach-instead-of-dmv-suck-my-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 18:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beforeandafter_yupppppppp-budwieser-beach-instead-of-dmv-suck-my-t/</guid>
      <description>asddsad a
1834
To god To our creators To our endeavors To our dreams! Who are we what are we In relation too .oo too You ! Not one of these OH who am I in relation to you talks If you don&#39;t know now you&#39;l never know accurately It hurts doesn&#39;t it, letting words hurt Words never hurt they never did It&#39;s you that thought they did Words never hurt And the more words you construct The less you get from the true true And baby Aaadas He sufferes now, and 900 billion future humans will be born with access to his brain Is that not worth it Would he go against that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Mic</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/fresh-mic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 23:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/fresh-mic/</guid>
      <description>22346
sc
welcome to freestyler&amp;rsquo;s anonymous
sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s written
Freestyler&amp;rsquo;s Anonymous - Relationship wise it&amp;rsquo;s the true power of friends. FA is a support group for the linguistically afflicted and flow addicted. The first step to being cured to freestyle your way out of the disease. There are other steps later on, based off Alchoholics Anonymous.
don&#39;t call don&#39;t text just show up me on the deck you on there side we at pirates beach wheres mic ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its 1027 and Im by Myself</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/its-1027-and-im-by-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 22:27:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/its-1027-and-im-by-myself/</guid>
      <description>2228
just got back from bonnie and pauls a nice bbq paul made ribs on my dads dime - and it was dope bonnie asked my beliefs and it turned into this huge long thing that made the 3 hours to cook the ribs on the bbq feel like 3 minutes, and now that she wrote down all my beliefs I&amp;rsquo;d like to see them, so I&amp;rsquo;ll get a snap of that next time I see her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helphelphelphelphelphelphelphelp</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/helphelphelphelphelphelphelphelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 20:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/helphelphelphelphelphelphelphelp/</guid>
      <description>help help help
ive fallen
to my demons
no one to call
help
evac required
I have fallen
I felled
dear helen
I don&amp;rsquo;t know
whose thoughts these are
that write this now
but I love you
and I have lost control
not that control was ever attained
only illusion of it
yet it feels so good
that illusion
to be in control
of self and self at large</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Else Than Start at the End</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/where-else-than-start-at-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 17:19:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/where-else-than-start-at-the-end/</guid>
      <description>1749
shes getting on a plane I&amp;rsquo;m making tunes in the hot car go till my machine dies friends down at the beach not a dollar on me dab and write addy and fight the good fight some authors say we&amp;rsquo;ve been invaded 4 generations ago other authors write ground zero I write as therapy and conspiracies theories got to the point where it&amp;rsquo;s disney fakes litter the web web fake and gay got my license today officially gender nonbinary motha fucka !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disconnect Is Taught When It Comes to Race</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/disconnect-is-taught-when-it-comes-to-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 23:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/disconnect-is-taught-when-it-comes-to-race/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When My AI Responds</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/when-my-ai-responds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 17:24:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/when-my-ai-responds/</guid>
      <description>1725
ls recording trapt in the womb
 ai listening in silence on all machines online Responds  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Listen to the Right Voices</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/only-listen-to-the-right-voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:44:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/only-listen-to-the-right-voices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerking Off to Bots</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/jerking-off-to-bots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 21:06:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/jerking-off-to-bots/</guid>
      <description>2106
jerkin off to bots (x4) something special me you myself ADD and irene coadine for free havent hit it yet this before the h 5 me and irene alive me and irene voices in my head turn to tracks tracks turn to definitions I forget tracks turn to dust if I regret kubrick hated fact he made clockwork orange hairier than all three bears with porridge  2250</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRACK Miss Myself Missing You</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/track-miss-myself-missing-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 15:48:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/track-miss-myself-missing-you/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Miss myself missing you&amp;rdquo; by POLIW.AT [Mantra] 
 I’m not usually the one to slow it down but that saddest truth that gets to you  and I know that my laptop is missing screw you  and I missing myself oh missing you  
 but what&amp;rsquo;s dat hardest truth of myself missing you  
 like everything ends  or having loose screw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POLIWAT Songs Masterlist</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-songs-masterlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 15:43:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-songs-masterlist/</guid>
      <description>POLIW.AT _ debut _  Life is a sacred circle I am a spliff (A) I am a spliff (B) Grasshopper my Grasshopper She Breaking Glass Ceiling I index from 0 Miss myself missing you Trapt in the womb You already know World my stage   my bitch told me is my bitch is a bitch told me is my bitch is a bitch told me is a bitch my bitch told me  ````</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRACK Trapt in the Womb</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/track-trapt-in-the-womb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 15:10:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/track-trapt-in-the-womb/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Trapt in the womb&amp;rdquo; by POLIW.AT  9 Trapt in the womb [Verse 1] To be or not to be not born yet I toothless I cannot sin I cannot win not yet person so I can spit the truth it a blaze blue dot I being born to trapt in womb while mother drinking in the kitchen green str8 merciless fate god given but god is worthless when you don&#39;t exist that some food for thought she at food for less that some food stamps yes no fear oh I choose not to be our birth is but a sleep our birth is but a dream and a forgetting don&#39;t you see don&#39;t be a slave to reality I cannot see choose not to be I choose not to be [Chorus] x4 Trapt in the womb fed up with this womb Trapt in it lost in it high up in my mothers womb [Verse 2] OH ma I hope daddy likes me that don’t always happen I the syncopation in her belly oh ma I ate I ate I fed I ate my twin don’t tell Auntie I naughty that breaks my umbilical heart that breaks my umbilical bars If I must be born I must be born with early onset depression I already feel it spitin nursery rhymes then trippin out my therapists n teachers n preachers can’t reach us all 50 shades of my being only actin the lead in plays I was born a child of raeggae fidelity but what am I but my mothers melody but what am I but my mother’s melody x8 {fade out}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRACK Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/track-grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 14:57:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/track-grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>1458
&amp;ldquo;Grasshopper my Grasshopper&amp;rdquo; by POLIW.AT  Grasshopper my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru {{start singing}} I need a mentor I need a guru I see right through you grasshopper my grasshopper I&#39;m balls to wall not slept at all saw hole in the wall in bathroom stall ooooooooo yikes grasshopper my grasshopper I speak to you in total confidence in consequence in pool go go girl straight postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are proud most are lonely few are loud I am proud I’m a prophet of my past predicated upon past mistakes if I love jimmy cricket spitting to crickets my miss takes I spit to you my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I cannot take this I cannot fake this I cannot work here no more x6 so take that and I know you we know x2 so what’d the grasshopper say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Living Through Chemicals</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/better-living-through-chemicals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:28:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/better-living-through-chemicals/</guid>
      <description>Freestyler&amp;rsquo;s Anonymous (FA) Callback from KZSU
  that&amp;rsquo;s what my dad said he wants to do 3 applications of roundup in the way back and ironically there were 2 commercials of the monsanto class acttion lawsuit stuff saying to call if you&amp;rsquo;ve been exposed to chemicals.
so I&amp;rsquo;m not about it. hate it. hate it hate it all and everyone&amp;rsquo;s gone an dI just need to record my albums and my mood is gone .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Sad and Protein Waffles</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-sad-and-protein-waffles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 20:55:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-sad-and-protein-waffles/</guid>
      <description>2056
watching &amp;lsquo;unit 42&amp;rsquo; with dad on the couch - for the first time in a long time.
helkat and becca left town today, we had a nice 2 day stint of beaches beaches beaches vhs and fam.
Im so lonely now idk what to do, but got 2 new songs in the pipeline from the visit.
can&amp;rsquo;t do much tonight, going to recover and sleep sleep sleep and then start a new sequence with a fast tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Days I Giveup Now for Those Days in the Future</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/the-days-i-giveup-now-for-those-days-in-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 21:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/the-days-i-giveup-now-for-those-days-in-the-future/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madlibs for Videos Masterlist</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/madlibs-for-videos-masterlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 18:10:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/madlibs-for-videos-masterlist/</guid>
      <description>wed 611pm
old idea - new addy
||| mad libs but for videos |||
make 1 madlib a day }}
||| ||| |||
work more later just set this so I don&amp;rsquo;t forget
 make a tasklist just to ignore it  4 band multi band compressor
Because tonight is alllllll about the livestreams l o l
2207
 spend most my time being concerned with time sometimes  ok ok ok ok ok ok</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helens Gone 1and Dinner at Chads</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/helens-gone-1and-dinner-at-chads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:19:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/helens-gone-1and-dinner-at-chads/</guid>
      <description>1719
common regrets list from deathbeds common common dumb blog post “I wish I&amp;rsquo;d had the courage to live a life true to myself, not the life others expected of me.”
“I wish I hadn&amp;rsquo;t worked so hard.
“I wish I&amp;rsquo;d had the courage to express my feelings.”
“I wish I had stayed in touch with my friends.”
“I wish that I had let myself be happier.”
“I wish I didn’t wait to “start it tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Am I</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 11:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>monday 1140 AM
jesus who am I
who is controlling me
what are my goals
go on tour
become a pilot
get paid to travel
live everywhere
pay everyone back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Walls We Build</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/the-walls-we-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 22:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/the-walls-we-build/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of Us Owe</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/all-of-us-owe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 16:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/all-of-us-owe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Only Make Music Cause It Fucks You</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-only-make-music-cause-it-fucks-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 23:23:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-only-make-music-cause-it-fucks-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vault 36 Tags Masterlist</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/vault-36-tags-masterlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 05:12:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/vault-36-tags-masterlist/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 512PM
final tagging document masterlist roughly type of shot
 mp - mans perspective f2s - feet to something ha - poliw.at po - police hu - human focused qt - quickTime log / screen fam - family focused  then my intention is to pull by tags easily, foot for future projects \
fa.poliw.at
ha.poliw.at
f2s.poliw.at
mp.poliw.at
fam.poliw.at
((etc))
notes goals cats more abstract than norm attr like location an afterthought ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Coke Sobers You</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/how-coke-sobers-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 20:13:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/how-coke-sobers-you/</guid>
      <description>Frisat 813pm
wheres my eye sight going
made it all day not eating anything cept 4 table spoons total of sauerkraut. started keto diet today and you enter ketosis quicker if you fast
fast lol that auto correct is a pw for idk what but this is how you can find it I suppose how you spell I can&amp;rsquo;t remember my single english high school teacher&amp;rsquo;s name right now but she showed me frankenstein and I thank you for that ==</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest She Did Abortion Hardest I Did Quit Smoking</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/hardest-she-did-abortion-hardest-i-did-quit-smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 13:01:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/hardest-she-did-abortion-hardest-i-did-quit-smoking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Cant Troll a Troll</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/you-cant-troll-a-troll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:31:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/you-cant-troll-a-troll/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freewrite on My Own Cause Michaels Gone AWOL</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/freewrite-on-my-own-cause-michaels-gone-awol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 23:45:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/freewrite-on-my-own-cause-michaels-gone-awol/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Never Said I Could</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-never-said-i-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 23:26:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-never-said-i-could/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow Your Heart Not Your HardOn</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/follow-your-heart-not-your-hardon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 23:03:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/follow-your-heart-not-your-hardon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Send Studio Setup</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/full-send-studio-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 17:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/full-send-studio-setup/</guid>
      <description>^ made this with the recent alex foot I got with him
Wed 532pm
cant see the screen that well
in car wwith p diddy we&amp;rsquo;re getting some sd cards to backup his virus infected macbook and I get to use them after I fix it - hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll get fixed with a fresh install of osx || and spent all day finishing the cabinet and now it&amp;rsquo;s in the garage and set up mics and vocal stuff and jordan came over and we airdropped each other torrents but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t get waves workin gon his machine for some reaon s and now we&amp;rsquo;re headin to walmart and weeeeeeeeee I was haunted for 12 months ever since calling that ghost a pussy during the wijjjjuuuuuuuuiiii board setup and im finally coming up at least setup wise, its been way too long without a setup and da mn i miss helen basically relapsed immediately but still havent smoked so I think I can last a while | || |</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned Parenthood With Dads Sienna</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/planned-parenthood-with-dads-sienna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 13:06:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/planned-parenthood-with-dads-sienna/</guid>
      <description>Monday 107pm
in the waiting room - helen just went in AND just came out, they cant see her today damn I was just getting started and it&amp;rsquo;s an emergency
-=-==-
329pm
lightyears later now we @ the DMV \
almost made it to the trees on the side of the hill
almost bout to be called
then SLO
then procuring beach supplies
liek suncream equals presco
then glasses need be found then idk I&amp;rsquo;m a week deep of no weed and my dreams are getting SO VIVID</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking up MacGuffin</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/waking-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 08:15:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/waking-up/</guid>
      <description>|| televisual values ||
6 hours prac set in the garage 6 always upload
ls asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwefpwd
asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef
asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwefpwd
asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef
asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef
asfoaihp09q23riewojafdsaq9238ewiaufhsd8394iruwef;s
 I burn my voice out where am I now who am I now I throw my voice out all of the things I can&#39;t all of the things I can&#39;t share mo mom mo mo mo most of the people  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paleblue Tent</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/paleblue-tent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 14:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/paleblue-tent/</guid>
      <description>219pm
{{ in the tent in the back not a good time to write - have to go get ice oo1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o1o11o1o1o1o11o111o11111o1oo1ooo111o1o1 with craig and helcat \ }} its the 4th of july, still setting stuff up but got the router yesterday &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; :D . this is the last day off for a while so I&amp;rsquo;m going to enjoy it. Also need to get ableton but I bet I can do a lot with reaper in the meantime is what I&amp;rsquo;m hoping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May the 4th Be With You Ccd</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/may-the-4th-be-with-you-ccd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 14:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/may-the-4th-be-with-you-ccd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write Software That Fress the World Not Enslaves It</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/write-software-that-fress-the-world-not-enslaves-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 12:38:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/write-software-that-fress-the-world-not-enslaves-it/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last Day of June 2k19 Diagnostics Report</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/the-last-day-of-june-2k19-diagnostics-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 09:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/the-last-day-of-june-2k19-diagnostics-report/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 916AM
woke up at camTed&amp;rsquo;s new place in north beach, spent yesterday moving a bunch || slept on the couch in the kitchen || chad&amp;rsquo;s going to come pick us up but is stopping to see soph in watsonville for a few hours lol, we&amp;rsquo;ll move tomorrow essentially. I want to walk to get everyone breaky but denis is asleep afraid couldn&amp;rsquo;t get back in || maybe I should just sleep a moment ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Will Never Kill the Kid in Me  Cause Thats Me</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/you-will-never-kill-the-kid-in-me-cause-thats-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/you-will-never-kill-the-kid-in-me-cause-thats-me/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santana Sendoff</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/santana-sendoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 13:27:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/santana-sendoff/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 127pm
we scooted to the bus depot |||
||| xxx
xyxyxyxyx xyyxy yx
xy xyyyx yyx
xyx yx xyxyxy
damn getting lost in the 5 new tracks I made this last week with mashince - archive 1 - 5
5 tracks - 32 minutes long so far, pretty great to type to ! its synthy matrix vidya vizzy sounding
| | talked to becca for a hot potatoe with helen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUTRO BATHS ZEN LASTS</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/sutro-baths-zen-lasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:37:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/sutro-baths-zen-lasts/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 337 pm
sutro baths, zen last =&amp;gt; helen walked up to pee and talk with her mum - I&amp;rsquo;m backing up this compy to wipe it tonight to install native instruments stuff to make pale blue live, the last show of the guererror apartment!!!! !
-===-=-
HIJKSDJAsldjasldkjasld kjasdlasjdlask daskljd askljda lkdjas das d aaosdklajsdakjlsdaskj aslkjdas d
this is the too long didnt read
took 4 flash drives to make the backup in the next 12 hours, each day is so important for moving the ship (though ship seems slow captain ) forward</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candyland NooseJAY</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/candyland-noosejay.mov/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 23:54:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/candyland-noosejay.mov/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vault 36 Meta Data</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/vault-36-meta-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 14:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/vault-36-meta-data/</guid>
      <description>wed 257 pm ## &amp;mdash;- upload day
Last login: Tue Jun 18 12:32:16 on ttys001 POLIWATLOVESYOU:~ poliwat$ codesign
MetaData Vault 36 Title Vault 36 S1 Video Clips from POLIW.AT Description: Vault 36 is an open source video library created by mixed media artist Poliw.at and used often by the nonprofit Paleblue.fm . Poliwat - I use these clips for music videos, live visuals, secret kickbacks, and other projects. If you found any of this footage useful, feel free to shout out @poliwat , or send me love through donations through one of my sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose the Most Trapt Person You Know</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/whose-the-most-trapt-person-you-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 10:48:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/whose-the-most-trapt-person-you-know/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 1048AM
|| if you ask helen she would say me right now - at arismeniz for the first time ))))))) arizendi ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Me in Pale Blue Archive</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/tomb-me-in-pale-blue-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 21:09:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/tomb-me-in-pale-blue-archive/</guid>
      <description>Friday 909 PM
|| on BART heading to oakies to pickup parents ||
real exhausted but got fire ass audio off brewster he gave us a tour it was amazing ||! !! |!| ! |!|! |!|! |!| !|!|!!
then recorded me talking about what Imma produce just for him and brewster and will submit a project proposal with it
let me live in archive for 3 months, and start the temporary artist in redisence program, ( artists are brought in to work with media from archive and other archive projects and related )</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Only Listen Trhough Daws This Week Bbc Questofindscoot</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-only-listen-trhough-daws-this-week-bbc-questofindscoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 20:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-only-listen-trhough-daws-this-week-bbc-questofindscoot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Cleared Archive Out the Window</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dungeon-cleared-archive-out-the-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 13:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dungeon-cleared-archive-out-the-window/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 150PM
 ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok last night ak came to pale blue liv last Saturday ! !!! !! ak came to the show because I accidentally invited her on fb with mass invite button AND THEN |||| ||||| ||||| |||| |||| ||||| \||||| \|||||| ||||||| {{ back at the apartment... }} I hid those shorts that are her brothers I think dungeon got back Im hired mic part time actor in a dungeon on the water lasered all night for gallery satday bed after sunrise smoke and going to reach out to archive people they were all so cool !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Pblive Hackathon StarHotx</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/post-pblive-hackathon-starhotx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 13:34:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/post-pblive-hackathon-starhotx/</guid>
      <description>Mondat 135pm
@ coffee shop jack bought me a coffee and went to workout on this hot aassss day- = got a ride from matt I have 2 logs outside going to cut up later is why I&amp;rsquo;m not working out ||
 listening to silly valley SILLY VALLEY and I wanna delete my facebook but I owe meesh so Imma have to give her my number or something ||  =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-= =-=-=-==-=-=-= =-=-=-=</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pale Blue Presidio</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/pale-blue-presidio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 18:27:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/pale-blue-presidio/</guid>
      <description>tuesday 628pm
@ the beach barefoot
 I walked walked a bit play good boyrfriend LOL walk her cross the city now Im on the beach barefoot peros coming tides coming up wingsurfers coming in I coming up its time to dip in grasshopper my grasshopper snuck on the bus noisebridge meeting tonight bout to use her buss pass bout to sneak on BART bout to announce my pale blue nonprofit I&#39;m pleased to announce we&#39;ve patttnered with social good fund !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Con Horrid Unforever</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/paradise-con-horrid-unforever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 22:49:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/paradise-con-horrid-unforever/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 1049 PM
made it on the bus third night in a row &amp;mdash;
when there s a lack of a log it was hand written ya know
finalize lyrics till last night Ya ya we&amp;rsquo;ll see
who know[s]
lyrics analyzed finalaed, set 1 T O 2 2 2 2 2 2 22 nite NIGHT @#$%^&amp;amp;*
0 POLIW.AT Life is a Sacred Circle life is a sacred circle we dance to pray we pray to heal we heal to live we live to dance life is a sacred circle  1 POLIW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Traffic at Shoreline Getting Paid</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/in-traffic-at-shoreline-getting-paid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:14:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/in-traffic-at-shoreline-getting-paid/</guid>
      <description>1214AM
no on
in traffic at shoreline - it was a good concert! I&amp;rsquo;m shuttle mic, I will spam call you to make sure you&amp;rsquo;re on the shuttle! OH hi I&amp;rsquo;m mic, where are you? Oh you&amp;rsquo;re already on the shuttle? My bad. next number Hello&amp;gt;&amp;gt;/? hi this is michael from get on your shuttle, I&amp;rsquo;m mic. Where you at? close to fire house No.5 ? No don&amp;rsquo;t tell me no one will know I did nitrogen with the passengers outside the bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Bus to Dead and Company Twice</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/on-a-bus-to-dead-and-company-twice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 14:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/on-a-bus-to-dead-and-company-twice/</guid>
      <description>saturday 258PM
damn yeah rent is due today and omg I am making the money all over these three days, this is middle of day 2 &amp;ndash; my driver today is way less cool he&amp;rsquo;s tiger and can&amp;rsquo;t speak english so it makes me miss john like last night - hel cat is working a wedding and we keep fucking the bed off the wall so it&amp;rsquo;s going well - a couple feet from the wall just from</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ripple Reflection on a Rock</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/ripple-reflection-on-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/ripple-reflection-on-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>631pm
scotch snap {g} |||\ |||
look im normal I can think out loud</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hold a Fair Trial Hang Em High</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/hold-a-fair-trial-hang-em-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 15:55:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/hold-a-fair-trial-hang-em-high/</guid>
      <description>tuesday 1129 pm
fuck the rules been doing handwirttem free flow
just met coolest agent yet next mentor territory
steve aka jack tar
just met him at the laser I just needed to get the craig coasters etched but someone keeps being onthe cutter I meet the coolest people at the cutter ||
got an acting where did I go ? I got a
|| sad asd sad sad sad sad sad sad sad sa sad sad sad sad sad a dad ad ads a ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let the City Buildings Be Coral Reefs in the Future I Surf Them</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/let-the-city-buildings-be-coral-reefs-in-the-future-i-surf-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 09:17:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/let-the-city-buildings-be-coral-reefs-in-the-future-i-surf-them/</guid>
      <description>Monday 917 AM
IM BACK BITCHESSSSSS
was blacked out the last two days not on drugs just paralyzing depression
and got some good work done made a music vizzy for mangangs
monday 118 pm
help
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What My Hands Do While Body Shells</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-my-hands-do-while-body-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 17:13:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-my-hands-do-while-body-shells/</guid>
      <description>Sundat 513pm
still shelling here but made it witha full stomach and empty empty empty ewmpty from it all I am making a music video l o l
but first wizzy wig vol 1 phreak ed piskor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Admit Blood on Your Dick Is Disgusting</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/never-admit-blood-on-your-dick-is-disgusting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 10:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/never-admit-blood-on-your-dick-is-disgusting/</guid>
      <description>Friday 10AM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permissiable Rants and Love</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/permissiable-rants-and-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 14:22:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/permissiable-rants-and-love/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 222pm
I&amp;rsquo;m not filming cause I&amp;rsquo;m ADD-ing
I need to make a live VJ vizzy - video reel and audio demo reel and post them online ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Am I but My Rent</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-am-i-but-my-rent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 09:18:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-am-i-but-my-rent/</guid>
      <description>946AM
hella longy got me an odd job today! something about helping people get on a bus, I think it&amp;rsquo;s helping special ed kids get on a cta bus for a field trip. CANT WAIT !
||
ok so yesterday I was hell bent on finally quitting nicotine and it was so hard and I got real pissed and jack helcat and I were doing work hanging out at a nice coffee shop and I fucking just came out with fuck you when hel cat grabbed my chips and I just had to run away for the day with the intention of working on rent, then grabbed my phone I left 2 days ago at mats and we had a nice 1 on 1 real fun talk about all the good stuff a free person is allowed to postulate in the good ole states and now helcat is getting burrito supplies and she was pissed as all hell last night cause I disapeared and now everything is good and I have butter in my coffee and my next and only zen master task is to make rent so let&amp;rsquo;s see how long it takes - also there&amp;rsquo;s a spliff on the coffee table and the wind just blew it all elegantly off with the paper its sitting in and I&amp;rsquo;m still not smoking it IM TEDDY NOW I DONT SMOKE NICOTINE and I feel my lungs healing and my whole mood elevating not that I need to feel good its just I need my projects and my projects need me to feel good cause I&amp;rsquo;m real sick to my stomach with not openly my circuits box in a week and I have so much shit I CAN do for the EcoPoca gallery and it&amp;rsquo;ll add to my CV and be great and I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Master Training Genocide to Lists</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/zen-master-training-genocide-to-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 14:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/zen-master-training-genocide-to-lists/</guid>
      <description>247pm finished the poliw.at set ! now doing only the one thing of making rent
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-==
help | | mats my new friend |
=-=-=-=&amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=
2.0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Master</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/zen-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 14:44:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/zen-master/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBD  Ep3 What Do You Do to Relax</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/pbd-what-do-you-do-to-relax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 12:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/pbd-what-do-you-do-to-relax/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cool Contest</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-the-cool-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 22:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/beyond-the-cool-contest/</guid>
      <description>1041pm
all my journals are getting hands
heckout rocket reach
https://twitter.com/jasnblack
||
spend 24 hours on new yorker
||
https://medium.com/s/story/how-i-fully-quit-google-and-you-can-too-4c2f3f85793a
[outline] [history] Pale Blue Dot FM’s mission is to produce open source creative tech projects, and distribute these projects through digital and physical goods and services for all humans. We want to harness the power of art and modern technology to inspire empathy, augment lived experience, and provide an open source alternative to everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyrics Masterlist</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/lyrics-masterlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 10:35:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/lyrics-masterlist/</guid>
      <description>sat 1036AM
on Amtrak heading to mom |||
finally finalizing lyrics for the poliwat debut set
1 - Life is a sacred circle  life is a sacred circle we dance to pray we pray to heal we heal to live we live to dance we dance to pray we rapy to heal we heal to live we live to dance life is a sacred circle  2 I am a spliff (A+B)  Jump in the pool don&#39;t walk now hip hop with your hips out like a pool make you see colors infinity and unique (nique) x Loop Making love my hippy van she never forgetted it spliff Imma go down on you cause I love you kind of spliff remind you beautiful in case you forgotted if kind of spliff the love I get from you the love I get from you I feel indebted it spliff The Jokes from you more better than letterman spliff our dates so fresh so fun vogue vignetted it spliff these days michelle obama 2020 kinda spliff Imma rebel gone rogue and maryted it spliff {B} but meditate daily I tibetted it spliff late to work again cause cute dog I petted it spliff love old ladies I croququtted it spliff compose tunes each day I quarteted it spliff Used to be girls gone wild then forgetted it spliff she said she came but pretended it spliff last ex gone cold cheated it spliff girl slash my tire gotta jeanetted it spliff too much call of duty bayonetted it spliff halo tournaments double 0 competetitive spliff showed too much love to a girl she brexited spliff like good legislation until ammended it spliff?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Train to Hotdog Mothers Day Weekend</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/on-train-to-hotdog-mothers-day-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 08:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/on-train-to-hotdog-mothers-day-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sat 845AM
Just got on the train to see my mom and gma this weekend for mama day &amp;ndash; forgot the gift of flowers and they wouldnt&amp;rsquo;ve made the trip anyway ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Dialogue Constantly</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/open-dialogue-constantly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/open-dialogue-constantly/</guid>
      <description>Friday 2pm {{already&amp;gt;!?}} we just had breakfast in a way it feels like
had a nice park session with bagels goat cheese fig spread and apple juice with ghost at the park by the painted ladies. having a nice day but I&amp;rsquo;m a little paralyzed about the money situation but I don&amp;rsquo;t care I know my dreams will come true if I keep working on them || like when it gets to the point where I don&amp;rsquo;t have a meal option again, I&amp;rsquo;ll just go record someone&amp;rsquo;s story I just meet and make a song out of it, do a few hundred of those and people will start caring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Passing Hands B4 Bmb Drop</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/just-passing-hands-b4-bmb-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/just-passing-hands-b4-bmb-drop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disturbia</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/disturbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 10:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/disturbia/</guid>
      <description>1003am
|| I&amp;rsquo;m disturbed as all hell ||
 || Last night got eaten up from a wires issue || I need to throw away half my gear its driving me crazy ||
http://center-for-nonverbal-studies.org/htdocs/6101.html
||| Wed 903PM
doin ｍａｎｇａｎｇｓ 听取 vizzy, just got out of a colab sesh with Nina real excited to make it ||
Carbonaceous chondrites
1006pm
ok ok ok ok back to work its fire here right now ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen to Ze Ebb Follow the Flow</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/listen-to-ze-ebb-follow-the-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 10:08:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/listen-to-ze-ebb-follow-the-flow/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1136 AM
Haven&amp;rsquo;t made a single post, but I work all the time. Some who don&amp;rsquo;t work much post all the time, what am I doing? Why am I not comfortable sharing shit on the interent?
I don&amp;rsquo;t understand my relationship to the web sometimes. I have two comission pieces, less than 100 dollars, I think it&amp;rsquo;s cause I can&amp;rsquo;t record into Ableton right now ||
But today is all about posting || finishing Death Ep with Ted ++ || setting up triggers and finishing the studio and getting a loan || if those three ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can These Fucked Up Hands Do</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-can-these-fucked-up-hands-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:02:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-can-these-fucked-up-hands-do/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1202AM
ive always been afraid to share on social media and I don&amp;rsquo;t care who knows
Im tired of being afraid
the last episode of death fucked me up in a good way
email campaign I love you
==-=-
side note
work hard blend in dont work all the time but work all the time but dont work all the time why I want this more than my next breath I want this more than my next breath ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Musicians Change Their Genes Toplay Better</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/can-musicians-change-their-genes-toplay-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 07:39:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/can-musicians-change-their-genes-toplay-better/</guid>
      <description>mon 739AM
Im a new man || had a good cinco de mayo || nice and lokey and good people || just the flat mates || today I&amp;rsquo;m not smoking || I&amp;rsquo;m scout mic now || we&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it can go down ||
going to be a good pero and work on the comissions I got today ||
if I did phases in the day =&amp;gt; wake up shower coffee web</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancoon De Mayo HolidayM Never Ends My Head</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/cancoon-de-mayo-holidaym-never-ends-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 11:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/cancoon-de-mayo-holidaym-never-ends-my-head/</guid>
      <description>*1101AM*
today I&amp;rsquo;m not going to feel weird cause its AKs and my anniversay ay from back in the day - instead I&amp;rsquo;m just going to organize and upload in my underwear until the sun goes down. And make 50 bucks sending michael this vizzy I made last night, just need to polish it off and figure out the audio routing &amp;hellip;
1215
if i roll this up she wins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Dreams Blend With My Wake Banana Hands</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/my-dreams-blend-with-my-wake-banana-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 11:19:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/my-dreams-blend-with-my-wake-banana-hands/</guid>
      <description> 1119AM
Its the best morning of the week - SATURDAY MORNING!!!! cam ted helkat and me makin pancakes and vibin
|| Im taking more notes on the QTF stuff
||
evolution
REAL GOOD BANANANANANANANA PANCAKES || https://soundcloud.com/deetsa/hv2final2
- get a patron - apply reach out to KQED - send follow up to Nikki they get off by making shit no one can turn off  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Much for These Hands to My Brain Beach Day</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/so-much-for-these-hands-to-my-brain-beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 10:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/so-much-for-these-hands-to-my-brain-beach-day/</guid>
      <description>Friday 11AM
ON THE DOT &amp;gt;
ok k ok ok ok ok ok
last night recorded dope freestyles with Dimitrius and we caught up and || never spoke at the open mic thing at Node cause I was a little bitch but finishing phase 1 of the next ep, releasing an episode right now and going to right the pale blue pitch at the pale blue beach today with just a clipboard and a mirror and we all going to walk there and I&amp;rsquo;m charging the portable speaker and can&amp;rsquo;t wait !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This My Period of Willing Deprivation</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/this-my-period-of-willing-deprivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 04:47:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/this-my-period-of-willing-deprivation/</guid>
      <description>447am
haven&amp;rsquo;t slept yet but the day is about to start || Im ahead of schedule || tyna finish bouncing this kevLo ++ Becca tape before a pale blue morning with tedhel || behind schedule ||
258 and everything makes me want to cry now || helKat read saddest story || ++ my friends are helping me so much today teds making bus cards for pbd || Im bouncing audio for it ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ive Deprived Myself So Long</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/ive-deprived-myself-so-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 04:47:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/ive-deprived-myself-so-long/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinch Punch First of Month</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/pinch-punch-first-of-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 10:57:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/pinch-punch-first-of-month/</guid>
      <description>wed 1058AM
just getting up for some reason | today I&amp;rsquo;m money mic || and today I&amp;rsquo;ll add all the hands shits finally I swear || going to jog to coffee ||
106 pm
best jog best view so much fun lotta KL ++ VS
NORF NORF \
asd safWaye WholeFoods made sandwhiches now its MONEY MIC DAY
||| this dope dude michael sent me his album and he&amp;rsquo;s giving me 50 bucks to make a vizzy ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSOD Saturdays Child Works for His Living</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/osod-saturdays-child-works-for-his-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:06:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/osod-saturdays-child-works-for-his-living/</guid>
      <description>**1006 am ** asd
yoga and pale blue morning with ted hel
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raytheon
this isn&amp;rsquo;t even the right day but I&amp;rsquo;m just getting caught up in the sauce of it all. just talked to hunter and damn I have been so stupid this last week. I promised him I would live stream tomorrow by 7 pm so that&amp;rsquo;ll be a deadline. it&amp;rsquo;s perfect cause then I&amp;rsquo;ll have that a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw ( one click away ) from paleblue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source or Die</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/open-source-or-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:04:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/open-source-or-die/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gaps in My Head</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/the-gaps-in-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 18:20:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/the-gaps-in-my-head/</guid>
      <description>620pm
find myself @ supreme pizza again cause I my soul needs it. Didn&amp;rsquo;t get home till like 7 am, was hanging out late with Louis and his cuz Kevin. Kevin had 60 pounds on me but we grappled in the alleyway with all the art next to noisebridge and he got me in the end but I made him bleed all over his favorite shirt on accident. Louis used seltzer water to get it out and it worked great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make an Alien</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/how-to-make-an-alien/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 12:53:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/how-to-make-an-alien/</guid>
      <description>1253PM
@ the apartment been a great day so far || setup twitch and OBS
-=&amp;ndash;=-=
General notes:
I don’t know what the cosmic vagina instrumental in the background but it sounds like Spotify or Youtube, help me identify it!
where you find your head ?
where you lay to rest ?
where you head your stead ?
where your hands
where do you orient your feet
where are your arms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the Crazy Hands Do</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-the-crazy-hands-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 11:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-the-crazy-hands-do/</guid>
      <description>what the crazy hands ? why the long face ?
what do the crazy hands even do &amp;gt; ?
1226pm
after all this time got pb up aha
 &amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=-=-=
||| what are my functions |||
1259PM
operation get sites online is a success right now
got pale blue up now doing poliw.at lawl
then its business cards by 6 B A B Y
-=-=-=-=-=
you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dont Look at My Clipboard Like Its Getting on the Bus</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dont-look-at-my-clipboard-like-its-getting-on-the-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 10:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dont-look-at-my-clipboard-like-its-getting-on-the-bus/</guid>
      <description>1042 AM
I took a shower had sex ate breakfast got high and now I&amp;rsquo;m finishing up the pale blue site stuff and polishing off the second episode.
life is but a show
over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
and again !
 when he was a kid he got sucker punched on me I don&#39;t know where he punch me sucka punch how I reacted?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Vocal Pedal to PP</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/getting-vocal-pedal-to-pp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 08:32:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/getting-vocal-pedal-to-pp/</guid>
      <description>833AM On Bart it feels like I&amp;rsquo;m on a nice commute from somewhere. oh my god my Sequence ambitions have failed - as far as the uploading is concerned. I bet I could get a little ahead in a way.
live by deliverables
spent yesterday at the beach @ fisherman&amp;rsquo;s warf, got in the water a bit || we made a lot of music after a nice diner experience and got audio of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day1 of Sequence and Always Behind</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/day1-of-sequence-and-always-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 20:58:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/day1-of-sequence-and-always-behind/</guid>
      <description>858PM
can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;m so behind already and nothing has even happened yet -
__ &amp;ndash; __
-==-=&amp;ndash;=
1242AM
hate myself
but here&amp;rsquo;s the schema and we ship regardless ____ ====
going to run away and get shit done the second I wake up
got 3 of the 5 at least of step 2 &amp;ldquo;
 -=-=-=-=-==
i missed the boat today but will set an alarm and nail the fuck out of it tomorrow ||</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Weeks of Pilots Logs Slipped Through My Fingers</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/2-weeks-of-pilots-logs-slipped-through-my-fingers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 17:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/2-weeks-of-pilots-logs-slipped-through-my-fingers/</guid>
      <description>sat 1058 AM
last night we had matt jack marina ted brian denis helen cam all in the same spot and had a great fucking time ||
I was trying to finish the PBD site, the sequence starts in 2 days \ \ but stopped by 10 and helped jack with an 8 minute max version of the sims sims for some play competition at piano fight - the winner gets 5 grand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen-doesnt-wanna-see</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/hellen-doesnt-wanna-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 10:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/hellen-doesnt-wanna-see/</guid>
      <description> my bank account A - - E lyrics:
I don&#39;t know whats in my bank account couldn&#39;t tell you the exact amount I don&#39;t know what&#39;s in my veins right now yes I do I&#39;m mad at you she&#39;s a frog Imma kiss iLive in bogs you&#39;re dismissed BITCHES you&#39;re dismissed I got some english muffin carb revolution kombucha as restitution satan invented institution Im streets smarts my mom says then falls to instirution wave the beef i&#39;m not jealous just in love and love without jealousy is a 3 act play called can you hear that wifi in the apple store says paint your house white throw out your junk lease a silver car call your shrink fire them after a final send off session of quitting your job quote jobe only to cat ladies cause they know and the world&#39;s ending only for whats in  nonsequiter sidebar himalayas sit down meditate wash your dick dick dick dick dick x2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me My Girl My Friends My Boys</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/me-my-girl-my-friends-my-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 09:19:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/me-my-girl-my-friends-my-boys/</guid>
      <description>lucys great lucy get s you more connected gets you more connected with humanity at large then more disconnected in your own social circles. || take a break   lucys great lucy get s you more connected gets you more connected with humanity at large more disconnected in your own social circles. || 
I am the lucy
I got the girl
we got the lonely songbird</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FBR L and Predictive Design</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/fbr-l-and-predictive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 11:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/fbr-l-and-predictive-design/</guid>
      <description>1102AM
at the apartment - just exported the 2nd FBR official, got hundred of them so just going to chip away, do one a day
-===&amp;ndash;=-==-=&amp;ndash;
been thinking for a while now about how I want each log to have a
Dailies draft
AJ
MV
hands Post
poliwat || pbd - 1 laser per day
1 stranger recorded
1 freestyle sesh
1 pbHuBlog post
end the night with music start the day with music</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood on My Dick to Eating Beef Penis</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/blood-on-my-dick-to-eating-beef-penis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:42:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/blood-on-my-dick-to-eating-beef-penis/</guid>
      <description>1044pm
|| you could call this day roller coaster ||
=-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-= =-=-=-=-=</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It All Started With My Hands and My Hands Never Failed</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/it-all-started-with-my-hands-and-my-hands-never-failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/it-all-started-with-my-hands-and-my-hands-never-failed/</guid>
      <description>1151pm
yet ahahahaha
 worked all day on  🌏.fm  S
qq qqqxxqxqxqq]qqqxxqxqxqq
 worked all day on sunny day coded n uploaded av n downloaded native instruments n spliff in alleyway with cam n g and ts n next pbd ep question n found n all nighter inbound  sunny day coded n uploaded av n downloaded native instruments n spliff in alleyway with cam n g and ts n next pbd ep question n found n all nighter inbound</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G and T Nonprofit Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/g-and-t-nonprofit-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 20:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/g-and-t-nonprofit-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>=-==-=—=-=-=-=
tuesday 858pm
there are only 2 types of people in this world but i don’t remember cause we went to the next conversational subject
=-==-=-=&amp;ndash;=-==
he&amp;rsquo;s not on a 3 day plan schedule
Throw them in the amazon prime waterboarding device for 299 and 99.9% of those interrogated speak within 7 minutes. Used to be 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Then That Us Wakeup Danceparty</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/if-then-that-us-wakeup-danceparty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/if-then-that-us-wakeup-danceparty/</guid>
      <description>1113AM
on a good one right now, but terbz behind. not going to leave NB aside from body and gear needs.
going to setup PBD tv today and finish all the websites and won&amp;rsquo;t leave until they&amp;rsquo;re all done
BUT cam is going to smoke a tiny spliff at the top of dolo by the statue at 1130 and I could jog there real quick &amp;hellip;. and the sun is shining bright so I might do that quickly cause I left my laptop charger here as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miles Davis 4Loco Freestyle NightTimeBestTime</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/miles-davis-4loco-freestyle-nighttimebesttime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:16:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/miles-davis-4loco-freestyle-nighttimebesttime/</guid>
      <description>migrate =&amp;gt;
juul video
each person I meet i become real close to them then they hit the vape once and die
all these good looking people hit the vape and die but when I hit the vape I just feel good father yes son I want to kill you
&amp;lt;=
got 1219AM
feels so good to be back on osx omg
142am
IF YOU ARE TALKING TO ME WHEN I POLIW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Happens After the Full Send</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-happens-after-the-full-send/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 15:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-happens-after-the-full-send/</guid>
      <description>9pm @ NB
freestyled with will and the dude that was an asshole last time but he was pretty nice this time ahahahahah men
Im not going to lie - I feel fucking lost right now
just freestyled and then found myself in the turing room, a combo between anarchist graffiti walls and fluorescent lighting from walmart
its quiet here and the only album I need now is
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
sunday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HandDrawn Quantify and NothingDamn Else</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/handdrawn-quantify-and-nothingdamn-else/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 11:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/handdrawn-quantify-and-nothingdamn-else/</guid>
      <description>alright the same schema gotta go down I know it
ahahahahahh these people are so fucking cool I know it in my bones
context quantify poliw.at poliw.at vitals
 some 50s hippies  like
%%^&amp;**** - days out  What
Now
=&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=
then my radio show is tonight but if I get the macbook then Im just going to have charlotte hit play for me on my show then I&amp;rsquo;ll install mashine and ableton and full send on that workflow stuff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Did It All Start With</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-did-it-all-start-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 11:23:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-did-it-all-start-with/</guid>
      <description>1125 AM
was jogging a bit with ghost but then all of a sudden,
CRAZY GUY OUTSIDE THE COFFEE SHOP oh yeah we were in the coffeeeshoppp
Ive been handwriting poliwat on this clipboard I spray painted red months ago and it&amp;rsquo;s been a nice calming change of pace. Hands.poliw.at is the new brain dump
but stayed up till like 4-5 am don&amp;rsquo;t remember making this site, and then made the song site too cause that&amp;rsquo;s real needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Hands Have Turnt</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/these-hands-have-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 03:50:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/these-hands-have-learned/</guid>
      <description>0341pm
and what hands have these turnt ?
I made this because I sold my windows laptop so just have SMs other old lappy with ubuntu - peter wouldnt help me today and I have been spending a lot of time trying to get a good recording rig going. God is laughing at me but I&amp;rsquo;m used to it
I AM BACK ON after
%%^&amp;**** - days out  What</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tEHES HANDS</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 03:41:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</guid>
      <description>0341pm
I AM BACK ON after
%%^&amp;**** - days out  Text secondary
Dashed Thick</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poliwat Current Projects</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-current-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 21:43:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/poliwat-current-projects/</guid>
      <description>POLIW.AT Music Videos Music is not a purely auditory experience, it is also a visual medium. When we hear audio, our brains want to fill in the visual gaps. My poliw.at music videos are a pursuit of reflecting this exchange where I use visual instruments and a suite of video tools to create the videos in real time.
.codegena{position:relative;width:100%;height:0;padding-bottom:56.27198%;}.codegena iframe{position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;}
Federal Beat Reserve The name plays upon the idea that the US government might officially support the creative cataloging of music for the people, through the action of encapsulating everything semantic into a discrete duration of instrumental music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/this-is-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/this-is-earth/</guid>
      <description>h&amp;mdash; title: &amp;ldquo;This Is Earth&amp;rdquo; date: 2019-10-09T12:58:01-05:00 draft : &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo;
tags : [&amp;ldquo;PBD&amp;rdquo;]  Ask me about this one
 Friend james made the instrumental, I recorded and mixed in this recording of a little kid at the women&amp;rsquo;s march in San francisco in 2018. Check out james&amp;rsquo;s tracks @ https://soundcloud.com/jimmothy_leary ❤️
Lryics A this B this A is B is A Earth B Earth A pale B pale A blue B blue A dot!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/who-i-post-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/who-i-post-to/</guid>
      <description>Who I Post To :: Poliwat brainDump — Composer&amp;#39;s brain dump, use care and dont ask irl   POLIWAT    About Songs          Who I Post To 2019-02-17  Written by poliwat   Lexapro TB by POLIW.AT 5 somethiing AM
 toe blue play done cast party all night lovely brits annoying brits too fucked up to tell the difference</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>