<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>schizop on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/tags/schizop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in schizop on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/tags/schizop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is a Sacred Circle</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:21:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</guid>
      <description>  Lyrics life is a sacred circle we dance to pray we pray to heal we heal to live we live to dance life is a sacred circle   Originally recorded on the beaches of Lake Superior from Cathy Nelson, and she played her flute. This is an old prayer from the Lacota Tribe, a native people before the United States.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>1603
 (V Vamp) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I see right through you oh Grasshopper my Grasshopper I&#39;m balls to wall not slept at all at mall saw hole in bathroom stall yikes that&#39;s not my verse! (V1) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I speak to you in total confidence from consiquence in pool go go girl straight postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are proud most are lonely few are loud I&#39;m proud I&#39;m a prophet of my past predicated on past mistakes if I love jiminy cricket spitting to crickets my mistakes I spit to you my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I cannot work here no more x6 I know you know we know x2 So what&#39;d the grasshopper say michael my michael You in a fix you need a fix double down on that double dick  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>