<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>song on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/tags/song/</link>
    <description>Recent content in song on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 22:01:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/tags/song/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All Song Wiki</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/songbook-master-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 19:24:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/songbook-master-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chords, sheet music, charts, and reference audio or video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is a Sacred Circle</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:21:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What began the second wave.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Piece of Man Is Work</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/what-a-pieve-of-man-is-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:00:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/what-a-pieve-of-man-is-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your final TODO list before you cut your cucumber off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Night I Got Old Yeller</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/night-i-got-old-yeller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 22:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/night-i-got-old-yeller/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cause I wrote about this youth paraphernalia in the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- description here  --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2202&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it was my room soooo&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;time? In the room dad died, bonjo just texted me saying I can&amp;rsquo;t make music here I barely read her little drama paragraph -  mom just talked shit for over an hour on the phone to her and all she had resources for was sending a text. FYI I never read long drama texts, that&amp;rsquo;s why my smile crinkles are coming in full swing early like a big band. And the band plays on. I think I&amp;rsquo;m more angry than sad that I can&amp;rsquo;t do a serious recording session in the room my dad died, when he bought me a nice scarlet interface to record with from the hopsice bed when I was taking care of him, I didn&amp;rsquo;t ask for it, he just surprise got it for me. And I found tears in my eyes at the beach today, meditating day two of sobriety feeling high as shit and the tears were more from the sunscreen why god every time I put sunscreen on my tears come? If I wanna cry about dad I&amp;rsquo;ll ask find the sunscreen. I&amp;rsquo;m too rushed right now to even eorry about it, no longer angry no longer sad, I&amp;rsquo;m miles, planets away from the fight with mom this morning, I&amp;rsquo;m out of this solar sytem, I&amp;rsquo;ve ran away with the van and the music equipment and played everywhere from madison to the sidewalks and I came back and bought the house and kicked out mom and put her in her new modest beach house and I turned the green room I painted I sit in now into a studio so I could record my best songs in the spot he died.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mason Dixon Line</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/mason-dixon-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 16:41:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/mason-dixon-line/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All I love and lost, not cause they died.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song Island</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/song-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 10:15:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/song-island/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sequel to &amp;lsquo;My Social Island&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toe Blue</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/toe-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 18:18:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/toe-blue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHEATERS, how do you justify cheating?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Whaling Erotica</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/on-whaling-erotica/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:27:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/on-whaling-erotica/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poem for h on whaling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theres a Trumpet Thats Ablazing</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/theres-a-trumpet-thats-ablazing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:23:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/theres-a-trumpet-thats-ablazing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the earliest hh explorations, gosh 7 years ago now?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Out for Cigs</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/media-out-for-cigs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:20:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/media-out-for-cigs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For those with writers block, read old meta notes(orkys).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dont Talk What You Can Show</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/dont-talk-what-you-can-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 11:16:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/dont-talk-what-you-can-show/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time to take some of your own advice, &amp;lsquo;Money Mic&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Push or to Stretch It Out Further</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/to-push-or-to-stretch-it-out-further/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:22:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/to-push-or-to-stretch-it-out-further/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Should I push what I know or stretch it out farther?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Therefore</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/therefore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:15:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/therefore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Real old attempt at breaking logic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And Then There Was Fire Ass Pixels</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/and-then-there-was-fire-ass-pixels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 21:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/and-then-there-was-fire-ass-pixels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First time drinking in a whole foods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surfing in the Sea</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/surfing-in-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:45:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/surfing-in-the-sea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Perfect song for the beach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Was Wandering in My Head</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/i-was-wandering-in-my-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:35:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/i-was-wandering-in-my-head/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another one about the dance between idealized, physical, metaphysical reality in cognition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seize the Day Girl</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/seize-the-day-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:14:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/seize-the-day-girl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great lick, lyrics did not stand the test of time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Talking Smiling Keeping</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/walking-talking-smiling-keeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 20:08:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/walking-talking-smiling-keeping/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The immortal feeling of mortality directed in this abstract love song with pokemon references.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking Down Central Park</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/walking-down-central-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 19:39:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/walking-down-central-park/</guid>
      <description>1939
(Verse 1) G C D Walking down central park and oh it&#39;s mighty dark please don&#39;t hurt me bum you can have all my money just don&#39;t take any of my precious pride and gum cause I got a date tonight oh with one hell of a site best I&#39;ve done in a while I care to admit with a pretty face and even better smile (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die (Verse 2) G C D I&#39;m ex military too I lied and said told that bum with a karate kick too the head then a sideways judo chop on his knee Can&#39;t fight just what I saw from MTV (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die (Verse 3) G C D Well that&#39;s the story enough&#39; said Now it&#39;s time to tuck you in bed Time to sleep this songs done and that&#39;s the story of how I met your mum (Chorus) G F C The last thing I need is a black eye doesn&#39;t even matter how hard you try doctors and lawyers still don&#39;t know why isn&#39;t it funny we still die we still die  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books as Monopods</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/books-as-monopods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 22:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/books-as-monopods/</guid>
      <description>lyrics; I use I use I use I use books as monopods they my monopods thats why my tunes got pops learned to love em ((unconditional))2 why ever since high school love was loving the weakness a little Leutenant Dan in me even if you missing legs and my fingers missing girls and my girls missing fingers and I know I will say anything just to feel this and to steal it away that&#39;s the moment today notha fucking hotel indoor bathroom window aye aye thats all you need for some therapy thats what I learned from motha fuckin symphonies that are silent not a single word though that&#39;s the fucking point that&#39;s why I listen though hm there&#39;s always time to shut the fuck up when you screaming on the inside its hard to keep it in oh what up Imma mother fuckin break it down I never slow down I never throw out even without a paddle now and I&#39;m still kicking rowing everybodys throwing stones I don&#39;t fucking feel it OH no drama that&#39;s a fucking joke yeah turn around I&#39;m sharper than a cutco and you know this composer time is fucking with the past and the present and the future in the same fucking context damn then I go and change it every fuckin few moments that&#39;s why I go fast (holy shit) that&#39;s why I need a lot of fucking friends I gotta lotta love to give and not a lot ways to and a lot of ways to express it this is fucking spring street I will fucking drive them downtown when I would feed needa needa a escape up in high school today I talkin act before I fucking ditched yesterday bonnie said psychedelics ruined my life mom said I used to be so fucking nice till went to santa cruz {lindsey called it lindsey called it lindsey called it} &amp;gt; santa booz and you know that I went hard (V2) but the friends and the skills acquired easily worth the cost I&#39;d do it ten times over it if hell freezes over non apathetic I take the cost damn dead it&#39;s priceless every single moment reprogram your brain then when you fuckin hate this subject yourself to fuckin challenge everyday get addicted to it I&#39;m not afflicted to it throw me in the coffin 7 days I won&#39;t lose my fucking mind today what kind of teacher and preacher could&#39;ve fucking preach that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:03:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>1603
 (V Vamp) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I see right through you oh Grasshopper my Grasshopper I&#39;m balls to wall not slept at all at mall saw hole in bathroom stall yikes that&#39;s not my verse! (V1) Grasshopper my Grasshopper I speak to you in total confidence from consiquence in pool go go girl straight postal in my post office be super nice cause most are lost most are proud most are lonely few are loud I&#39;m proud I&#39;m a prophet of my past predicated on past mistakes if I love jiminy cricket spitting to crickets my mistakes I spit to you my grasshopper I need a mentor I need a guru I cannot work here no more x6 I know you know we know x2 So what&#39;d the grasshopper say michael my michael You in a fix you need a fix double down on that double dick  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Time I Go Out Imma Teach Got a Lesson</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 19:18:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/next-time-i-go-out-imma-teach-got-a-lesson/</guid>
      <description>[chorus] next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson next time I go out Ima teach God a lesson gotta lesson from the drunk shaman well tortured to death there&#39;s snow on his sleeve I make a plan to fuck for a living believe wouldn&#39;t you these discoveries my discoveries stop pissin on mom so next time I go out Imma leave a note pro bono bonobo in peripheral tho goa koa my homie hobo as of late they my therapy today I need it i breath it I Greg Elementary my dear watson The ABCs of Boy Love  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Irish Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/my-new-irish-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:34:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/my-new-irish-sing-along/</guid>
      <description> lyrics your youth drink but 1000 times let us clink our drinks tonight my soul your soul your soul mine! share dare stare drink all the wine!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wash Your Acapella</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/song/wash-your-acapella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 11:20:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/song/wash-your-acapella/</guid>
      <description>#lyrics
(verse 1) Himalayas sit down meditate ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 2) At work bathroom stall sit down take a piss ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 3) get a text she met her ex sit down ((wash your dick dick dick wash your dick)) x2 (verse 5) Now she home give kiss stab back ((wash your dick dick dick wash your knife)) x2 (verse 6) Dig hole what she wanted pray to God ((wash your dick dick dick watch your back)) x2 (verse 7) it was a dream she still alive thank god ((and wash her clit clit clit wash her clit )) x2 (verse 8) me on a rock in spacew kill the snakes [and] ((wash your mind mind mind wash your mind)) x4  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>