<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:28:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three Rs Diagnosalis</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/the-three-rs-diagnosalis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:28:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/the-three-rs-diagnosalis/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I Read You This to Start Your Day</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/can-i-read-you-this-to-start-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 11:32:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/can-i-read-you-this-to-start-your-day/</guid>
      <description>11:39AM
|| &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo; arises, not in the dumb parts that make the sum, but in the complex patterns they organize themselves in ||
Kinda like the &amp;lsquo;i&amp;rsquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t completely exist until your &amp;lsquo;i&amp;rsquo; in every possible universe is in conversation
oh ye whose says I s no I s as anything to do with my body, I reckon.
Her sold soul swells hell high watermelon wheat on tap
 &amp;quot;&amp;quot;&amp;quot;methinks my my body is but the less of my better being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One True Holiday</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/one-true-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 15:28:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/one-true-holiday/</guid>
      <description>@ LA museum where jack and I danced years ago
surprised he called it a treasured memory.
Me and Helcat ate at cantor&amp;rsquo;s and god damn I had the pastrami reuben and have been high ever since. Real
I like these swivel chairs more than that art on the walls
oh this will fuck us up
always talking enthusiastically about how something&amp;rsquo;s going to fuck me up, like this black Yerba Mate Tea, this lavender spray, this homemade kombucha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truth Today Lies Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/truth-today-lies-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:15:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/truth-today-lies-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>life today lies tomorrow sleep today lies tomorrow king lion today lies tomorrow wow look at this room full of great books I cant read  .. LOVE IT OUT HERE ..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Trip Mid Awning Project</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/la-trip-mid-awning-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 12:11:23 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/la-trip-mid-awning-project/</guid>
      <description>1212
About to get picked up by http://robbieconal.com/about/robbies-bio/ || never net him or his wife Debbie but they&amp;rsquo;re so nice to pick me up !
Helen said don&amp;rsquo;t be racy ahahahaha I&amp;rsquo;m not more racy than anyone else - everyone&amp;rsquo;s racy || that&amp;rsquo;s the thing ||
Trying to get some polecat in but Im too excited to go down and take a break from Nips I can&amp;rsquo;t wait :D There&amp;rsquo;s a bunch of instruments and an interface where we&amp;rsquo;re staying so I just want to record some new music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill Help You When You Prove Me Wrong</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/ill-help-you-when-you-prove-me-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 14:04:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/ill-help-you-when-you-prove-me-wrong/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It DO Returns</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/what-it-do-returns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 21:00:17 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/what-it-do-returns/</guid>
      <description>2100
cant write cause I&#39;m upset write cause I&#39;m upset I&#39;m wet swam a mile today can&#39;t imagine how I&#39;d feel if I didn&#39;t do that what can I finish what can&#39;t I when I can&#39;t seem to get anything done is what doing it feels like often all the time veteran in my mind and I wanna chat not bite  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Feeds to a Global Audience</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/best-feeds-to-a-global-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 16:05:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/best-feeds-to-a-global-audience/</guid>
      <description>CHAD polecat and I met on chat roulette, we both rapped at each other
Lowkey worker 1
LOWKEY WORKER 1 She said she&amp;rsquo;s going to be late should I lock her out?
LOWKEY WORKER 2 Unacceptable
-=-=-
and I couldn&#39;t hold my fast going to a new cafe known for healthy sandwhiches and just ordering more caffeine seemed dumber than when you don&#39;t want to spend money but if you have to before you come home you drink Lowkey worker 2 she walk in great tits cute asiam im looking for a book that as you read it it feels like my nonlabelist life partner gross&#39;s ass cheeks are completely settled on my face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Im Not Working Today and Im Not Working</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/im-not-working-today-and-im-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 14:50:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/im-not-working-today-and-im-not-working/</guid>
      <description>14:50
I&amp;rsquo;m not working today and I&amp;rsquo;m not working and I am not working and by the way, and look and what else can I say I refuse to buy anything on black friday but craig is shopping now so he&amp;rsquo;s keeping an eye out for
&amp;lsquo;pants that will make helen&amp;rsquo;s pussy wet&amp;rsquo; 2 pairs of slim fits I can bring to New york, on sale, and I&amp;rsquo;ll give him the cash tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didn T Get Soaked Till the End of the Pier</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/didn-t-get-soaked-till-the-end-of-the-pier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:26:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/didn-t-get-soaked-till-the-end-of-the-pier/</guid>
      <description>13:53
Didn’t get soaked till the end of the pier&amp;hellip; so dropped helcat off at grover beach train station, walked pismo and got to the end of the pier. I read the letter freewrite I wrote on the plane from chicago when I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I was going to make it to my dad in time. Well I fucking made it and he made it one more month and I was there all the time and slept in the room and felt beyond horrid on the couch at myself for not giving him mouth to mouth in his last moments when he said he couldn&amp;rsquo;t breath, and I just fucking hate myself for it and the fine line between hating oneself and loving oneself someone tell me cause I walked pismo without a mind just lead by the theatre of my feet, my feet as a submarine after it rained there, me in all black 3 layers of cotton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grieg Takes Me Thankskilling Shopping</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/grieg-takes-me-thankskilling-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 14:01:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/grieg-takes-me-thankskilling-shopping/</guid>
      <description>1401
I hit the table why’d you do that ? why’s your face look like that ? why you not talking? why you talking so much? she da queen da queen da queen of why why this? why that face? why you weird? why you here? why you not here? why aren’t aren’t you working why you working?  -=-=-=- -=-=-=- -=-=-=- -=-=-=- -=-=-=- -=-=-=- helen said memoirs are fiction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thats What Wearing the Pants Mean</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/thats-what-wearing-the-pants-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:14:17 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/thats-what-wearing-the-pants-mean/</guid>
      <description>but i didn&amp;rsquo;t say anything stupid like that&amp;rsquo;s how I get better or it soothes my soul or its a deal breaker or any of that shit || I just left it clear and stear way like the way the rich around me allow me to really be DGAF and write and I love it and I neer got drunk at a whole foods and doubt this will be the night cause 4 ipas down I&amp;rsquo;m on a good one, not drunk just gotta piss - down to go start drinking so red flag or green flag I&amp;rsquo;m all of them until I&amp;rsquo;m caught by some producer or someone rich or the AUGsyDHJKAN operatives that run the show &amp;lt;3 so signing off more songs to ahiUDJSKN {write!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Banned Words</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</guid>
      <description>..and no bad days == 1750 h got me a beer and we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to freewrite to warm the engines up but I&amp;rsquo;m really just gunning for helping her and then doing god knows what on the website, just the savage new hip hop mantra, results and go go go and things that don&amp;rsquo;t take so long and such == and I got to thinking about this old man here and everyone at the kreautburg we&amp;rsquo;re sitting in and helen&amp;rsquo;s looking at my screen and I&amp;rsquo;m just fucking stoked it&amp;rsquo;s christmas on fucking november sunday 552 pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Mom and Bonnie</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 13:05:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</guid>
      <description>Dear mom and bonnie, I love you, I want to support yo both, but I&#39;m clearly adding stress to both of your lives. I came here to help dad, I was hoping to stay a few weeks, maybe up to xmas to show support and for us to grieve together. It&#39;s too short a time to rent somewhere else in the area, and I need to be in the city to move my career forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up From Strange News From Another Star</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:14:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</guid>
      <description>1015AM
finally a timestamp
\
that was a month where dtme
didnt exits
 death was life and life was death and they were locked together in an eternal mad lmove battle and this was the final word and the meaning of the world and thence came a radiance that could glorify all misery and thence came a shadow that trumpeted all joy and beauty but from out of this darkness joy burned more intimately and more beautifully and love had a deeper glow within this night -from flute dreams by herman hesse (Strange news from a another star)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who I Post To</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/who-i-post-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 12:07:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/who-i-post-to/</guid>
      <description>Lexapro TB by POLIW.AT 5 somethiing AM
 toe blue play done cast party all night lovely brits annoying brits too fucked up to tell the difference
who do I post make to i remember when i had a really good thyme it was very fruitful, just cuz if who knew knew I knew they knew then it wouldn&#39;t be hard to find post even a pigeon gets it no diss needed vague my only if you wanna make fun of people you need to talk to sam and sam only he&#39;s the best at making fun of people saturated in s god damn s no one knows the difference matter of time its the trickle down effect no one even bothers even when I spell it I&#39;m faithful of the trickle only a matter of time before the king gets abandoned for some better lute shallow depth as a front brute et tu as if you won the hoot patience that a virtue I told you when I wanted to ammend it I&#39;m done with the play and the play is haunting me I can&#39;t quit the play now that there isn&#39;t an excuse to spend so much time together so where do I post to when I can&#39;t even write the post who do I scream to when I couldn&#39;t get the vote Who will I become through chasing your soul why don&#39;t I care if you hurt me and go a moment with you is enough of the world the body mind and spirit yes, I said a moment with you and enough of this world why spend so much time on something bad who told me I&#39;d live this long without feeling this bad who killed Seinfeld a line I always fuck up nothing gets me out of head space to crawl up theres no amount of weed that could fuck me up harder than this holy dance break it off two days ago you crazy pants freestyle with naked guy with sunglasses in canon in the bathub do I feed her ego or feed anyone fishing for a compliment listening to tunes I made I done m.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>