<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://poliw.at/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:26:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://poliw.at/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Banned Words</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 17:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/death-of-banned-words/</guid>
      <description>..and no bad days == 1750 h got me a beer and we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to freewrite to warm the engines up but I&amp;rsquo;m really just gunning for helping her and then doing god knows what on the website, just the savage new hip hop mantra, results and go go go and things that don&amp;rsquo;t take so long and such == and I got to thinking about this old man here and everyone at the kreautburg we&amp;rsquo;re sitting in and helen&amp;rsquo;s looking at my screen and I&amp;rsquo;m just fucking stoked it&amp;rsquo;s christmas on fucking november sunday 552 pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Mom and Bonnie</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 13:05:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/dear-mom-and-bonnie/</guid>
      <description>Dear mom and bonnie, I love you, I want to support yo both, but I&#39;m clearly adding stress to both of your lives. I came here to help dad, I was hoping to stay a few weeks, maybe up to xmas to show support and for us to grieve together. It&#39;s too short a time to rent somewhere else in the area, and I need to be in the city to move my career forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up From Strange News From Another Star</title>
      <link>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:14:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poliw.at/log/waking-up-from-strange-news-from-another-star/</guid>
      <description>1015AM
finally a timestamp
\
that was a month where dtme
didnt exits
 death was life and life was death and they were locked together in an eternal mad lmove battle and this was the final word and the meaning of the world and thence came a radiance that could glorify all misery and thence came a shadow that trumpeted all joy and beauty but from out of this darkness joy burned more intimately and more beautifully and love had a deeper glow within this night -from flute dreams by herman hesse (Strange news from a another star)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>